#	字典配置表		
#	Key		Value
#	string		string
#	字典主键	策划备注	字典内容，可使用转义符
	LOBBY_NAME_1	排行榜	Ranking List
	LOBBY_NAME_2	福利中心	Welfare Center
	LOBBY_NAME_3	抽奖	Luck draw
	LOBBY_NAME_4	商店	Shop
	LOBBY_NAME_5	首冲礼包	First-line gift bag
	LOBBY_NAME_6	每日特惠	Daily Deal
	LOBBY_NAME_7	在线奖励	Online rewards
	LOBBY_NAME_8	七日登陆	7 days landing
	LOBBY_NAME_9	签到	Sign in
	LOBBY_NAME_10	月卡	Monthly card
	LOBBY_NAME_11	成长基金	Growth Fund
	LOBBY_NAME_12	激活码兑换	Activation Code Conversion
	LOBBY_NAME_13	活动	Activity
	LOBBY_NAME_14	竞技	Sports
	LOBBY_NAME_15	探险	Explore
	LOBBY_NAME_16	乱斗	Fighting
	LOBBY_NAME_17	排位	Ranking
	LOBBY_NAME_18	金币副本	Instance of gold coins
	LOBBY_NAME_19	经验副本	Instance of experience
	LOBBY_NAME_20	英雄	Hero
	LOBBY_NAME_21	任务	Task
	LOBBY_NAME_22	星图	Star map
	LOBBY_NAME_23	阵容	Lineup
	LOBBY_NAME_24	好友	Good friend
	LOBBY_NAME_25	英雄升星	A hero rises to the stars
	LOBBY_NAME_26	英雄进阶	Heroic Advancement
	LOBBY_NAME_27	英雄装备	Heroic Equipments
	LOBBY_NAME_28	英雄技能	Heroic Skills
	LOBBY_NAME_29	成长任务	Growth Task
	LOBBY_NAME_30	每日任务	Daily tasks
	LOBBY_DESC_1	解锁排行榜	Unlocking List
	LOBBY_DESC_2	解锁福利中心，大量福利领到手软	Unlock welfare centers and receive a lot of benefits.
	LOBBY_DESC_3	解锁抽奖，抽取SSR英雄	"Unlock Lottery, Draw SSR Heroes"
	LOBBY_DESC_4	解锁商店，购买稀有道具	Unlock stores and buy rare props
	LOBBY_DESC_5	解锁首冲礼包，充点小钱玩一玩	Unlock the first-line gift bag and fill it with small money.
	LOBBY_DESC_6	解锁每日特惠，超值礼包每日都有	"Unlock Daily Preferences, Value Bags Daily"
	LOBBY_DESC_7	解锁在线奖励，你的时间非常值钱	Unlock online rewards. Your time is very valuable.
	LOBBY_DESC_8	解锁七日登陆，连续7天，领取绝版英雄	"Unlock 7 days landing, 7 consecutive days, receive out-of-print Heroes"
	LOBBY_DESC_9	解锁签到。累计签到领豪礼	Unlock check-in. Accumulated Sign-in and Receive Honorable Gifts
	LOBBY_DESC_10	解锁月卡，每天钻石领到手软	"Unlock the monthly card, every day the diamond receives the soft hand"
	LOBBY_DESC_11	解锁成长基金，小投资，大回报	"Unlock Growth Fund, Small Investment, Big Return"
	LOBBY_DESC_12	激活码兑换	Activation Code Conversion
	LOBBY_DESC_13	更多精彩活动，等你一起参加	"More exciting activities, waiting for you to join us"
	LOBBY_DESC_14	解锁竞技场，证明自己的实力	Unlock the arena and prove your strength
	LOBBY_DESC_15	解锁剧情副本，挑战关卡，获取奖励吧	"Unlock Instance of the plot, challenge checkpoints and get rewards"
	LOBBY_DESC_16	乱斗	Fighting
	LOBBY_DESC_17	解锁排位，冲击全服第一	"Unlock position, impact full service first"
	LOBBY_DESC_18	解锁金币副本，每日挑战可获得大量金币	Unlock Instance of gold coins and get lots of gold coins on a daily challenge
	LOBBY_DESC_19	解锁经验副本，每日挑战可获得大量经验	"Unlocking Experience Instance, Daily Challenge Gains Much Experience"
	LOBBY_DESC_20	英雄	Hero
	LOBBY_DESC_21	任务	Task
	LOBBY_DESC_22	解锁星图，激活星图提升英雄战力	"Unlock Star Map, Activate Star Map, Promote Heroic Combat Force"
	LOBBY_DESC_23	阵容	Lineup
	LOBBY_DESC_24	呼朋唤友，并肩作战	Call for friends and fight side by side
	LOBBY_DESC_25	解锁英雄升星，高级英雄，从此开始	"Unlock Heroes, Star Up, Senior Heroes, Start from now on"
	LOBBY_DESC_26	解锁英雄进阶，扫荡副本材料可提升英雄品质	Unlocking heroes and cleaning duplicate materials can enhance heroic qualities.
	LOBBY_DESC_27	解锁英雄装备，强化精炼英雄装备提升战力	"Unlock heroic equipment, strengthen refined heroic equipment and enhance combat effectiveness"
	LOBBY_DESC_28	解锁英雄技能，镶嵌徽章，输出爆表	"Unlock Hero Skills, Insert Badges, Output Explosive Tables"
	LOBBY_DESC_29	成长任务	Growth Task
	LOBBY_DESC_30	完成每日任务，可获得高额奖励	High rewards for completing daily tasks
	GUIDE_DESC_10001	在虚空风暴的大陆上，存在着各种各样的遗迹，成功挑战可获得意想不到的收获哦，准备好和伊蕾莎一起大冒险了吗？	There are all kinds of relics on the continent of the Void Storm. Successful challenges can bring unexpected gains. Are you ready to take a big risk with Eliza?
	GUIDE_DESC_10002	遗迹中不仅有怪物的驻守，还有各种可怕的机关，当然副本里的瓶瓶罐罐打碎的话，有以外收获哦！	"There are not only monsters stationed in the ruins, but also various terrible organs. Of course, if the bottles and cans in the Instance are broken, there will be gains outside."
	GUIDE_DESC_10003	英雄每件装备都可以消耗金币进行强化哦，是不是很划算，注意的是，装备强化不能超过英雄的最大等级！	Every hero's equipment can be strengthened by consuming gold coins. Is it cost-effective? Note that the equipment can't be strengthened beyond the hero's maximum level!?
	GUIDE_DESC_10004	扫荡副本收集材料，可对英雄进行品质的提升，提升品质后的英雄会变得越来越强大！想要在这片大陆上立足，英雄提升品质必不可缺哦！	"Sweeping Instance and collecting materials can improve the quality of heroes, and the heroes will become more and more powerful after improving the quality! If you want to stand on this continent, it is essential for heroes to improve their quality."
	GUIDE_DESC_10005	小投入，大回报，高级抽奖可获得意外惊喜哦！这里有概率获得高级技能徽章，绝版英雄，稀有道具！来碰碰运气吧~~	"Small investment, big return, high-level lottery can be surprising! Here's the chance to get high skill badges, out-of-print heroes, rare props! Let's try our luck.~~"
	GUIDE_DESC_10006	获得新英雄后，可来这里更换自己喜欢的英雄，上阵的英雄可在战斗中切换出战哦！上阵英雄的战力总和就是玩家的战力哦！	"After gaining new heroes, you can come here and change your favorite heroes. The heroes in battle can switch out of battle. The total strength of the heroes in battle is the strength of the players."
	GUIDE_DESC_10007	我们的征途是星辰大海，挑战副本获得星图能量，激活星图能量可给每一个上阵的英雄属性加成！抽奖也能获得星图能量哦	Our journey is the Star Sea. Challenge the replica to get the Star Chart Energy. Activate the Star Chart Energy to add to every hero's attributes! You can also get star power by drawing a lottery.
	GUIDE_DESC_10008	在虚空风暴的大陆上，想要生存下去，结识一群可靠的伙伴是非常重要的。你可以在这里邀请其他玩家成为你的好友哦	"In the land of empty storms, it is very important to meet a group of reliable partners in order to survive. You can invite other players to be your friends here."
	GUIDE_DESC_10011	副本三星通过后，可快速扫荡，扫荡可获得副本奖励，免去繁琐的打怪过程哦！合理的扫荡消耗体力，这样才不会浪费哦！	"After the duplicate Samsung passes through, it can be quickly swept away, and the duplicate reward can be obtained for sweeping away, so as to avoid the tedious blame process. Reasonable sweeping consumes physical energy, so it won't waste!"
	GUIDE_DESC_10012	选择任意玩家进行挑战，挑战之前记得观察下对手的战力和上阵英雄，选择合理的整容和势均力敌的队友往往是获胜的关键哦！	"Choose any player to challenge. Before challenging, remember to observe the opponent's fighting power and heroes. Choosing reasonable cosmetic surgery and matching teammates is often the key to win."
	GUIDE_DESC_10013	装备精炼后可大幅度提升装备属性，同时也会让你的英雄变得更强，抽奖和商城都有几率获得装备精炼的材料哦！	"Equipment refinement can greatly improve the equipment attributes, but also make your hero stronger, lottery and shopping malls have the chance to obtain equipment refined materials oh!"
	LOBBY_DESC_31	解锁时空试炼，挑战可获得大量英雄碎片	"Unlock space-time trial, challenge can get a lot of heroic debris"
	LOBBY_DESC_32	解锁风暴之塔，战力越高，通关越多	"Unlock Storm Tower, the higher the fighting power, the more customs clearance."
	LOBBY_NAME_31	时空试炼	Temporal and Spatial Trial
	LOBBY_NAME_32	风暴之塔	Tower of Storm
