#	字典配置表		
#	Key		Value
#	string		string
#	字典主键	策划备注	字典内容，可使用转义符
	SKILL_NAME_10001	斩杀	Beheading
	SKILL_NAME_10006	正义打击	Justice Kill
	SKILL_NAME_10007	骑士之怒	Anger Of Knight
	SKILL_NAME_10008	圆桌裁决	Round Table Ruling
	SKILL_NAME_10009	圣光波	Wave Of Light
	SKILL_NAME_10088	闪避	Dodge
	SKILL_NAME_10101	燕人刺	Swallow Thorn
	SKILL_NAME_10106	链杀	Chain Kill
	SKILL_NAME_10107	影杀	Shadow Kill
	SKILL_NAME_10108	瞬狱杀	Prison Kill
	SKILL_NAME_10109	地震杀	Earthquake Kill
	SKILL_NAME_10188	闪避	Dodge
	SKILL_NAME_10301	双枪射	Double Shoot
	SKILL_NAME_10305	舞步射击	Dancing Shoot
	SKILL_NAME_10306	迷星杀阵	Fan Star Kill
	SKILL_NAME_10307	震地射击	Earthquake Shoot
	SKILL_NAME_10308	流星	Meteor
	SKILL_NAME_10388	闪避	Dodge
	SKILL_NAME_10401	基础奥术	Basic Arcane
	SKILL_NAME_10405	秘法球	Secret Spells Ball
	SKILL_NAME_10406	闪电风暴	Lightning Storm
	SKILL_NAME_10407	法力黑洞	Mana Leak
	SKILL_NAME_10408	雷神下凡	Raytheon Fall Down
	SKILL_NAME_10488	闪避	Dodge
	SKILL_NAME_10701	野蛮链球	Barbaric Hammer
	SKILL_NAME_10706	暴力弹射	Violent Ejection
	SKILL_NAME_10707	焦土	Scorched Earth
	SKILL_NAME_10708	铁链风暴	Chain Storm
	SKILL_NAME_10709	螺旋碾压	Spiral Rolling
	SKILL_NAME_10788	闪避	Dodge
	SKILL_NAME_10801	冰冰弹	Ice Bomb
	SKILL_NAME_10805	速冻炮	Quick Frozen Gun
	SKILL_NAME_10806	雪花喷射器	Snowflake Ejector
	SKILL_NAME_10807	超霸气制冷机	Super Gas Refrigerator
	SKILL_NAME_10808	冬天来啦	Winter Coming
	SKILL_NAME_10888	闪避	Dodge
	SKILL_NAME_10901	暗之鞭	Darkness Whip
	SKILL_NAME_10906	夜叉缠	Yaksha Twine
	SKILL_NAME_10907	无尽鞭挞	Endless Whipping
	SKILL_NAME_10908	阿修罗漩涡	Asura Vortex
	SKILL_NAME_10909	湿婆杀	Shiva Kill
	SKILL_NAME_10988	闪避	Dodge
	SKILL_NAME_11201	钢拳	Gouken
	SKILL_NAME_11206	火力球形态	Firepower Sphere
	SKILL_NAME_11207	能量过载	Energy Overload
	SKILL_NAME_11208	疯狂进军形态	Crazy March
	SKILL_NAME_11209	轰炸形态	Bomber
	SKILL_NAME_11288	闪避	Dodge
	SKILL_NAME_11401	埃及艳后连续技	Cleopatra Combo
	SKILL_NAME_11405	埃及艳后技能1	Cleopatra Skill One
	SKILL_NAME_11406	埃及艳后技能2	Cleopatra Skill Two
	SKILL_NAME_11407	埃及艳后技能3	Cleopatra Skill Three
	SKILL_NAME_11408	埃及艳后切换技	Cleopatra Switch Skill
	SKILL_NAME_11488	埃及艳后闪避技	Cleopatra Dodge
	SKILL_NAME_11501	枪术	Jousting
	SKILL_NAME_11506	寒刺	Cold Needling
	SKILL_NAME_11507	龙缠	Dragon Entangled
	SKILL_NAME_11508	破军之阵	Pojun Battle Formation
	SKILL_NAME_11509	天降寒星	Cold Star Fall Down
	SKILL_NAME_11588	闪避	Dodge
	SKILL_NAME_11801	喷毒	Spraying Poison
	SKILL_NAME_11806	剧毒导弹阵	Toxic Missile Array
	SKILL_NAME_11807	死亡喷射	Death Jet
	SKILL_NAME_11808	疯狂炼金师	Crazy Alchemy
	SKILL_NAME_11809	唯我毒尊	Poison Solipsism
	SKILL_NAME_11888	闪避	Dodge
	SKILL_NAME_12001	利刃.闪电	Lightning Blade
	SKILL_NAME_12005	人肉电桩	Human flesh Stake
	SKILL_NAME_12006	球形闪电	Kugelblitz
	SKILL_NAME_12007	电流潮汐	Current Tide
	SKILL_NAME_12008	星辰电海	Starry Sea
	SKILL_NAME_12088	闪避	Dodge
	SKILL_NAME_11601	基础剑术	Fencing
	SKILL_NAME_11606	光击斩	Light Chopping
	SKILL_NAME_11607	裂地斩	Ground Chopping
	SKILL_NAME_11608	幻影斩	Phantom Chopping
	SKILL_NAME_11609	破碎虚空	Space Broken
	SKILL_NAME_11688	闪避	Dodge
	SKILL_NAME_12101	泼墨退敌	Splshing Ink 
	SKILL_NAME_12105	飞龙在天	Dragon Fly
	SKILL_NAME_12106	妙笔生花	Couples
	SKILL_NAME_12107	墨海漩涡	Inkslab Vortex
	SKILL_NAME_12108	泰山压顶	Bear down Mount Taishan
	SKILL_NAME_12188	闪避	#REF!
	SKILL_DESC_1000101	挥舞大剑对前方目标进行连续攻击	Sword-wielding Continuous Attacks on Front Targets
	SKILL_DESC_1000601	向前方发出四个快速移动的攻击波攻击目标	Send forth four fast-moving attack waves to attack the target
	SKILL_DESC_1000701	通过连续点击对目标造成连续伤害	"Continuous damage to the target by continuous clicks

"
	SKILL_DESC_1000801	形成可移动的风火轮对目标进行连续攻击	Forming a movable wind turbine to attack the target continuously
	SKILL_DESC_1000901	跳出并蓄力，释放扇形冲击波	Jump out and gather strength to release sector shock wave
	SKILL_DESC_1008801	快速躲闪，避免受到猛烈攻击	Avoid fierce attacks by dodging quickly
	SKILL_DESC_1010101	手持双刃对目标进行连续攻击	Hand-held double-edged continuous attack on target
	SKILL_DESC_1010601	荆轲甩出三条铁链匕首攻击周围目标	Jing Ying threw out three iron-chain daggers and attacked the surrounding targets.
	SKILL_DESC_1010701	向前进行Z形快速突进	Forward Z-Shaped Rapid Progression
	SKILL_DESC_1010801	通过连续点击在目标附近穿梭并攻击目标	Shuttle around the target and attack the target by clicking on it continuously
	SKILL_DESC_1010901	荆轲从高空中跳出砸向地面目标	Jing Ke jumped out of the air and hit the target on the ground
	SKILL_DESC_1018801	快速躲闪，避免受到猛烈攻击	Avoid fierce attacks by dodging quickly
	SKILL_DESC_1030101	对目标进行持续而快速的射击	Continuous and rapid firing of targets
	SKILL_DESC_1030501	手持双枪并旋转着边移动边射击周围目标	Hold two guns and rotate while moving to shoot around the target
	SKILL_DESC_1030601	跳向前方并丢下炸弹袭击目标	Jump forward and drop the bomb on the target
	SKILL_DESC_1030701	释放五星结界持续燃烧目标并爆炸	Release Five-Star Junction Continuous Burning Target and Explode
	SKILL_DESC_1030801	如流星砸向地面攻击并燃烧周围目标	If a meteor strikes the ground and burns its surroundings
	SKILL_DESC_1038801	快速躲闪，避免受到猛烈攻击	Avoid fierce attacks by dodging quickly
	SKILL_DESC_1040101	对目标造成法术攻击，并释放雷电陷阱	Create magic attacks on targets and release lightning traps
	SKILL_DESC_1040501	释放雷电球，所到之处全部遭受雷电袭击	Release lightning balls and all places are attacked by lightning
	SKILL_DESC_1040601	雷电球高能放电，对目标进行电击	"Lightning Ball High Energy Discharge, Shock the Target"
	SKILL_DESC_1040701	梅林释放雷电黑洞，将目标吸入其中	Merlin releases lightning black holes and sucks targets into them
	SKILL_DESC_1040801	梅林旋于半空，召唤天雷击杀周围目标	"Merlin whirled in mid-air, summoning sky lightning to kill surrounding targets"
	SKILL_DESC_1048801	快速躲闪，避免受到猛烈攻击	Avoid fierce attacks by dodging quickly
	SKILL_DESC_1070101	用力甩出附火铁球对目标进行连续攻击	Continuous attack on the target by forcefully throwing out the iron ball attached to the fire
	SKILL_DESC_1070601	将附火链球狠狠的砸向目标，并将其拉回施以重击	Strike the fire-attached hammer hard at the target and pull it back for a heavy blow
	SKILL_DESC_1070701	通过连续点击使铁球频繁砸地对周围目标进行攻击	Attacking the surrounding targets frequently with continuous clicks
	SKILL_DESC_1070801	抡起铁球并快速旋转，边移动边攻击周围目标	"Pick up the iron ball and spin it fast, moving and attacking the surrounding targets"
	SKILL_DESC_1070901	突然冲出砸向地面，对周围目标进行持续攻击	"Suddenly burst out and hit the ground, continuing to attack the surrounding targets"
	SKILL_DESC_1078801	快速躲闪，避免受到猛烈攻击	Avoid fierce attacks by dodging quickly
	SKILL_DESC_1080101	手持寒冰枪对目标进行连续射击	Continuous firing of a target with an ice gun
	SKILL_DESC_1080501	蓄力并释放寒气攻击并冰冻目标	Store up and release the cold to attack and freeze the target
	SKILL_DESC_1080601	跳起并进行疯狂扫射，同时冰冻目标	Jump up and shoot frantically while freezing targets
	SKILL_DESC_1080701	释放超长冰气冲击波可移动中攻击目标	Release super-long ice shock wave to attack target in mobile
	SKILL_DESC_1080801	将武器砸向目标并进行疯狂扫射同时冰冻目标	Shoot weapons at targets and shoot frantically while freezing targets
	SKILL_DESC_1088801	快速躲闪，避免受到猛烈攻击	Avoid fierce attacks by dodging quickly
	SKILL_DESC_1120101	达芬奇驾驶机器人对目标进行连续攻击	Da Vinci Driving Robot Attacks Targets Continuously
	SKILL_DESC_1120601	变身可移动的战争机器，对周围目标进行扫射	Change into a mobile war machine to shoot at surrounding targets
	SKILL_DESC_1120701	达芬奇原地释放热能，对周围目标进行灼烧	Da Vinci releases heat in situ and burns targets around him
	SKILL_DESC_1120801	甩动两条机械臂并转动身体，通过移动攻击目标	Shake two robotic arms and rotate the body to attack the target by moving
	SKILL_DESC_1120901	达飞奇变身轰炸机对目标进行猛烈攻击	Da Feiqi's metamorphosed bomber attacked the target fiercely
	SKILL_DESC_1128801	快速躲闪，避免受到猛烈攻击	Avoid fierce attacks by dodging quickly
	SKILL_DESC_1150101	手持冰气长枪连续攻击目标	Continuous attack with an ice-air lance
	SKILL_DESC_1150601	向前进行快速突刺，攻击并冰冻目标	"Speed forward, attack and freeze targets"
	SKILL_DESC_1150701	召唤冰龙，边移动边攻击并冰冻目标	Call the Icedragon to attack and freeze the target as it moves
	SKILL_DESC_1150801	利用武器支撑身体并快速旋转，边移动边击杀敌人	"Use weapons to support the body and spin quickly, while moving and killing the enemy"
	SKILL_DESC_1150901	手持冰枪从空中冲下并旋转攻击目标	Hand-held ice guns rush down from the air and spin to attack targets
	SKILL_DESC_1158801	快速躲闪，避免受到猛烈攻击	Avoid fierce attacks by dodging quickly
	SKILL_DESC_1180101	喷射毒雾，对周围目标连续攻击	Spray poison fog to attack surrounding targets continuously
	SKILL_DESC_1180601	向周围释放的毒气罐会瞬间爆裂，击杀周围目标	"The gas tank released to the surrounding area will burst instantly, killing the surrounding target"
	SKILL_DESC_1180701	向周围持续喷洒毒气，毒杀目标	Continuous spraying of poison gas around the target
	SKILL_DESC_1180801	持续喷射毒气攻击周围目标	Continuous injection of poison gas to attack surrounding targets
	SKILL_DESC_1180901	跳起的瞬间扔下毒气罐，攻击周围目标	Drop the gas tank at the moment of jumping and attack the surrounding target
	SKILL_DESC_1188801	快速躲闪，避免受到猛烈攻击	Avoid fierce attacks by dodging quickly
	SKILL_DESC_1210101	使用毛笔凌空点划，对周围目标连续攻击	Continuous attacks on surrounding targets using brush strokes
	SKILL_DESC_1210501	向正前方释放数条墨龙，击退前方目标	Release several ink dragons in front of you to repel the target ahead
	SKILL_DESC_1210601	毛笔虚点，形成墨龙环绕周身，边移动边攻击周围目标	"The brush dots, forming ink dragon around the body, moving while attacking the surrounding targets"
	SKILL_DESC_1210701	神龙清官用力使用毛笔搅动地面形成黑色漩涡，将目标吸入其中并进行攻击	"Shenlong Qingguan used his brush to agitate the ground to form a black whirlpool, inhaling the target and attacking it"
	SKILL_DESC_1210801	神龙清官的令牌化为泰山般大小迅速砸击地面，攻击周围目标	"Shenlong Qingguan's token became the size of Mount Tai and quickly hit the ground, attacking surrounding targets"
	SKILL_DESC_1218801	快速躲闪，避免受到猛烈攻击	Avoid fierce attacks by dodging quickly
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_10001	"使用大剑连续劈砍，每个输出循环可造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。"	"Using a sword to chop continuously, each output cycle can cause `LC, DA, {0:#}` base damage.
"
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_10006	"向前方打出一道光波，可造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。"	"Shooting a light wave forward can cause `LC, DA,{0:#} `basic damage.
"
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_10007	"连续点击技。快速的挥舞大剑攻击敌人，连续按键可以增加攻击次数，最多可造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。"	"Continuous click technology. Rapid swords attack enemies. Continuous keystrokes can increase the number of attacks, causing up to `LC, DA, {0:#}` basic damage.
"
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_10008	"跳到空中，以剑刃风车的姿态攻击敌人，攻击时可以移动追击敌人，可造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。"	"Jump into the air and attack the enemy as a blade windmill. When attacking, it can move and chase the enemy. It can cause `LC, DA, {0:#}` basic damage."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_10009	"切换技。从天而降，向前方打出三道剑刃波，可造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害，并无视霸体使目标浮空。"	"Switching technology. Falling from the sky and striking three blade waves forward can cause `LC, DA, {0:#}` basic damage and make the target float regardless of the hegemony.
"
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_10088	向指定方向闪避4米距离。基础闪避能量600点，每次闪避消耗300点。可以通过装备徽章提高闪避能量和回复速度。	"Avoid 4 meters in the specified direction. Base evasion energy is 600 points, each evasion consumes 300 points. Avoidance energy and recovery speed can be increased by equipping badges."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_10101	"使用短刀连续攻击，每个输出循环可造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。"	"Each output cycle can cause `LC, DA, {0:#}` base damage by using a knife to attack continuously."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_10106	"向四周掷出链刃，造成连续伤害，随后将周围敌人拉至身边，给予强力一击。共造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。附带吸血效果。"	"Throwing a chain blade around, causing continuous damage, and then pulling the enemy around to give a powerful blow. Altogether cause `LC, DA, {0:#}` base damage. Incidental effect of blood suction."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_10107	"向前快速突刺，对直线上的敌人造成强力伤害，可将敌人击至空中。可造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。"	"Fast forward thrust, causing strong damage to the enemy in a straight line, can hit the enemy into the air. Can cause `LC, DA, {0:#}` base damage."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_10108	"连续点击技。在空中不断穿梭闪现形成杀阵，每次闪现造成一次伤害，连续按键可以增加攻击次数，共造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。附带吸血效果。"	"Continuous click technology. Continuous flickering in the air forms a killing battle. Each flicker causes one damage. Continuous keystrokes can increase the number of attacks, resulting in `LC, DA, {0:#} `basic damage. Incidental effect of blood suction."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_10109	"切换技。以迅猛之势从天而降，无视霸体眩晕目标并造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。"	"Switching technology. Falling from the sky with a rapid force, ignoring the hegemonic dizzy targets and causing `LC, DA, {0:#}` basic damage."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_10188	向指定方向闪避4米距离。基础闪避能量600点，每次闪避消耗300点。可以通过装备徽章提高闪避能量和回复速度。	"Avoid 4 meters in the specified direction. Base evasion energy is 600 points, each evasion consumes 300 points. Avoidance energy and recovery speed can be increased by equipping badges."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_10301	"使用双枪和步枪连续射击，每个输出循环可造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。"	"Using double guns and rifles to shoot continuously, each output cycle can cause `LC, DA, {0:#}` basic damage."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_10305	"双手持枪旋转射击，射击过程中快速移动，对周围目标造成伤害，共造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。"	"Two-handed revolving gun shooting, rapid movement in the shooting process, causing damage to surrounding targets, a total of `LC, DA, {0:#}` basic damage."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_10306	"使用火药在地面制造一个五星杀阵，对进入杀阵的敌人造成持续伤害，一段时间后杀阵爆炸。共造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。"	"Use gunpowder to create a five-star killing battle on the ground, causing continuous damage to the enemy who enters the killing battle, and then the killing battle explodes after a period of time. Altogether cause `LC, DA, {0:#}` base damage."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_10307	"跳跃至远处，同时使用步枪轰击地面，造成大量伤害，并在原地形成一个灼烧区域，对敌人造成持续伤害，共造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。"	"Jump to a distance, and use rifles to bombard the ground, causing a lot of damage, and in situ form a burning area, causing sustained damage to the enemy, causing a total of `LC, DA, {0:#}` basic damage."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_10308	"以火球形态坠落地面，造成大量伤害并消耗目标800点霸体值，并在原地形成一个灼烧区域，造成持续伤害，共造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。"	"Falling to the ground in a spherical form causes a lot of damage and consumes the target's 800-point hegemony value, and forms a burning area in the original terrain, causing sustained damage, resulting in `LC, DA, {0:}` basic damage."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_10388	向指定方向闪避4米距离。基础闪避能量600点，每次闪避消耗300点。可以通过装备徽章提高闪避能量和回复速度。	"Avoid 4 meters in the specified direction. Base evasion energy is 600 points, each evasion consumes 300 points. Avoidance energy and recovery speed can be increased by equipping badges."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_10401	"连续释放法术攻击，每个输出循环可造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。"	"Continuous release of spell attacks, each output cycle can cause `LC, DA, {0:#}` base damage."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_10405	"放出一个缓慢移动的巨大的法术球，对触碰到的敌人造成伤害，全部击中可造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。附带减速效果。"	"Release a giant magic ball that moves slowly, causing damage to the enemy it touches. All hits can cause `LC, DA, {0:#}` base damage. Incidental deceleration effect."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_10406	"向前方大面积敌人释放闪电链，对每个敌人可造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。附带减速效果。"	"Release lightning chains to large areas of enemies ahead, causing `LC, DA, {0:#}` basic damage to each enemy. Incidental deceleration effect."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_10407	"在原地释放一个法力黑洞，可以将附近敌人吸入黑洞内，并造成持续伤害，最多可造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。附带减速效果。"	"Releasing a mana black hole in situ can suck nearby enemies into the black hole and cause sustained damage, up to `LC, DA, {0:}` basic damage. Incidental deceleration effect."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_10408	"召唤天雷攻击周围目标并无视霸体使目标浮空，对每个敌人可造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。附带减速效果。"	"Call the Sky Thunder to attack the surrounding target and make the target float regardless of the hegemony. It can cause `LC, DA, {0:}` basic damage to each enemy. Incidental deceleration effect."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_10488	向指定方向闪避4米距离。基础闪避能量600点，每次闪避消耗300点。可以通过装备徽章提高闪避能量和回复速度。	"Avoid 4 meters in the specified direction. Base evasion energy is 600 points, each evasion consumes 300 points. Avoidance energy and recovery speed can be increased by equipping badges."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_10901	"使用鞭子连续攻击，每个输出循环可造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。"	"With whip attacks, each output cycle can cause `LC, DA, {0:#}` base damage."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_10906	"将身体周围敌人击远，并用鞭子缠绕住敌人，然后再快速拉回身边，给予强力一击。共造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。附带吸血效果。"	"Shoot away the enemy around you and wrap it around you with a whip. Then pull it back quickly and give it a powerful blow. Altogether cause `LC, DA, {0:#}` base damage. Incidental effect of blood suction."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_10907	"连续点击技。在原地用鞭子不断鞭挞敌人，连续按键可以增加攻击次数，最多可造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。"	"Continuous click technology. In situ whip constantly whipping the enemy, continuous keystrokes can increase the number of attacks, at most can cause `LC, DA, {0:#}` basic damage."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_10908	"使用鞭子制造一个暗影漩涡，把附近敌人吸入，不断地造成伤害，可以使用鞭子牵引漩涡旋转，最多可造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。附带吸血效果。"	"Use whips to create a shadow whirlpool, inhale nearby enemies, and constantly cause damage. Use whips to pull the whirlpool around, causing up to `LC, DA, {0:#}` basic damage. Incidental effect of blood suction."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_10909	"拉住鞭子在空中旋转踢击周围敌人，共造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。"	"Pull the whip in the air and rotate to kick the enemy around, causing `LC, DA, {0:#}` basic damage."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_10988	向指定方向闪避4米距离。基础闪避能量600点，每次闪避消耗300点。可以通过装备徽章提高闪避能量和回复速度。	"Avoid 4 meters in the specified direction. Base evasion energy is 600 points, each evasion consumes 300 points. Avoidance energy and recovery speed can be increased by equipping badges."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_11201	"使用铁拳和机枪连续攻击，每个输出循环可造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。"	"Using iron fists and machine guns, each output cycle can cause `LC, DA, {0:#}` base damage."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_11206	"变形为球形态，使用机枪射击在前方形成火力压制，球形态下会持续快速移动，可以手动控制移动方向。球形态总共可输出`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。"	"Deformation into a spherical shape, the use of machine gun fire in front of the formation of fire suppression, spherical shape will continue to move rapidly, can manually control the direction of movement. The spherical shape can output `LC, DA, {0:#}` base damage."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_11207	"蓄力技。按住技能按钮可进入能量过载状态，松开按钮将能量释放对周围敌人造成伤害，过载时间越长，造成伤害越高。最高可造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。附带灼烧效果，对目标施加持续伤害BUFF。"	"Intensive skill. Press the skill button to enter the energy overload state. Loosen the button to release the energy and cause damage to the enemy around. The longer the overload time, the higher the damage. Maximum damage `LC, DA, {0:#%}` base damage. Incidental burning effect, inflicting BUFF on the target for sustained damage."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_11208	"将铁拳放出，身体快速旋转，带动铁拳形成大范围的伤害，疯狂进军形态下会持续快速移动，最后一击附带灼烧效果。可以手动控制移动方向。最多可造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。最后一击附带灼烧效果，对目标施加持续伤害BUFF。"	"The iron fist is released, the body rotates rapidly, and causes the iron fist to cause extensive damage. It will continue to move rapidly in the form of crazy march, and the last blow will have a burning effect. The direction of movement can be controlled manually. At most `LC, DA, {0:#%}` base damage. The last blow is accompanied by a burning effect, which inflicts BUFF on the target for sustained damage"
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_11209	"以轰炸形态，对地面进行十字形地毯攻击，并在轰炸区域留下灼烧区域，可造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。轰炸区域附带灼烧效果，对目标施加持续伤害BUFF。"	"A cross carpet attack on the ground in bombing mode, leaving a burning area in the bombing area, can cause `LC, DA, {0:#}` basic damage. Burning effect is attached to the bombing area, and BUFF is applied to the target for sustained damage."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_11288	向指定方向闪避4米距离。基础闪避能量600点，每次闪避消耗300点。可以通过装备徽章提高闪避能量和回复速度。	"Avoid 4 meters in the specified direction. Base evasion energy is 600 points, each evasion consumes 300 points. Avoidance energy and recovery speed can be increased by equipping badges."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_11501	"使用长枪连续攻击，每个输出循环可造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。"	"Each output cycle can cause `LC, DA, {0:#}` base damage by using a long gun to attack continuously."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_11506	"持枪快速向前突刺，对一条直线上的敌人造成伤害并将其冰冻，可造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。突刺附带冰冻效果。"	"Shooting forward quickly with a gun, causing damage to an enemy in a straight line and freezing it, can cause `LC, DA, {0:#}` basic damage. The protrusion is accompanied by a freezing effect."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_11507	"舞动长枪召唤寒龙，脚踏寒龙快速移动，对敌人造成伤害并将其冰冻，可以手动控制移动方向，最多可造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。突刺附带冰冻效果。"	"Dancing a long gun calls the dragon to move quickly, causing damage to the enemy and freezing it. It can manually control the direction of movement, and at most cause `LC, DA, {0:#}` basic damage. The protrusion is accompanied by a freezing effect."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_11508	"使用长枪撑地急速旋转，形成一个伤害漩涡，可以手动控制移动，结束一击发出冻气，可以将周围敌人冰冻。最多可造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。结束一击附带冰冻效果。"	"The use of long gun support to rapidly rotate, forming a damage whirlpool, can manually control movement, end a blow to send out frost, can freeze the enemy around. At most `LC, DA, {0:#%}` base damage. End one hit with freezing effect."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_11509	"从天而降，用枪尖撑地高速旋转，随后落地并用枪砸击地面，共造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。结束一击附带冰冻效果。"	"Down from the sky, spin at high speed with the tip of the gun, then land on the ground and hit the ground with the gun, causing `LC, DA, {0:#}` basic damage. End one hit with freezing effect."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_11588	向指定方向闪避4米距离。基础闪避能量600点，每次闪避消耗300点。可以通过装备徽章提高闪避能量和回复速度。	"Avoid 4 meters in the specified direction. Base evasion energy is 600 points, each evasion consumes 300 points. Avoidance energy and recovery speed can be increased by equipping badges."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_11801	"使用毒液喷射器和毒瓶连续攻击，每个输出循环可造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。"	"Continuous attacks with poison ejectors and bottles can cause `LC, DA, {0:#}` basic damage per output cycle."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_11806	"从天空向地面发射数个巨大毒瓶，每个毒瓶会造成持续伤害，并令目标中毒，4秒后所有毒瓶爆炸，造成大量伤害。每个毒瓶可造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。"	"Several huge poison bottles were launched from the sky to the ground. Each poison bottle would cause sustained damage and poison the target. After 4 seconds, all the poison bottles exploded, causing a lot of damage. Each poison bottle can cause `LC, DA, {0:#%}` base damage."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_11807	"从毒液喷射器中喷出大量毒火，击中目标后可以吸血，如果击中中毒目标，吸血量会大幅提升，喷射过程中可以转向。最多可造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。全程附带吸血效果。"	"A large amount of poison fire is ejected from the poison ejector, which can suck blood after hitting the target. If the poisoned target is hit, the amount of blood will be greatly increased, and the injection process can be diverted. At most `LC, DA, {0:#%}` base damage. The whole course is accompanied by blood sucking effect."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_11808	"连续点击技。从身体中不断喷出大量毒瓶，攻击大范围内的敌人，同时令目标中毒。连续按键可以增加喷射次数。最多可造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。"	"Continuous click technology. A large number of poison bottles are constantly ejected from the body, attacking enemies in a wide range, and poisoning the target. Continuous keystrokes can increase the number of shots. At most `LC, DA, {0:#%}` base damage."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_11809	"从毒雾中出生，随后将周围敌人拉至身边，给予强力一击，并令目标中毒。可造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。"	"From the poisonous fog, the enemy will be pulled to the side, give a strong blow, and poisoning the target. Can cause `LC, DA, {0:#}` base damage."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_11888	向指定方向闪避4米距离。基础闪避能量600点，每次闪避消耗300点。可以通过装备徽章提高闪避能量和回复速度。	"Avoid 4 meters in the specified direction. Base evasion energy is 600 points, each evasion consumes 300 points. Avoidance energy and recovery speed can be increased by equipping badges."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_11601	"使用太刀连续攻击，每个输出循环可造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。"	"With Taidao continuous attack, each output cycle can cause `LC, DA, {0:#}` base damage."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_11606	"按住技能按钮可进入蓄力状态，松开按钮剑豪宫本武藏化为光芒飞击出去斩杀目标，最多可造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。"	"Press the skill button to enter the storage state. Release the button and turn Jianhao Miyamoto Musashi into a light flying to kill the target. At most, it can cause `LC, DA, {0:#}` basic damage."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_11607	"使用太刀猛斩地面，将周围地面碎裂以伤害目标，可造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。"	"Using the Taidao to chop the ground and break up the surrounding ground to damage the target can cause `LC, DA, {0:#}` basic damage."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_11608	"宫本武藏化为幻影，连续斩击周围目标，造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。"	"Miyamoto Musashi transformed into a phantom, chopping off surrounding targets continuously, causing `LC, DA, {0:#}` basic damage."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_11609	"大剑豪破碎虚空从天而降，裂地并给予强力一击。之后连续快速斩击三次，可造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。"	"Dajianhao broke the void and fell from the sky, cracked the ground and gave a powerful blow. After three consecutive quick chops, can cause `LC, DA, {0:#}` basic damage."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_11688	向指定方向闪避4米距离。基础闪避能量600点，每次闪避消耗300点。可以通过装备徽章提高闪避能量和回复速度。	"Avoid 4 meters in the specified direction. Base evasion energy is 600 points, each evasion consumes 300 points. Avoidance energy and recovery speed can be increased by equipping badges."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_10701	"使用链球连续攻击，每个输出循环可造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。"	"With continuous hammer attacks, each output cycle can cause `LC, DA, {0:#}` base damage."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_10706	"将链球大力击出，攻击直线上的敌人，随后跃到空中将链球拉回，同时将直线上的敌人拉倒身边，给予强力一击。总共可造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。结束一击区域附带灼烧效果。"	"Strike the hammer hard, attack the enemy in the straight line, then jump into the air to pull the hammer back, while pulling the enemy in the straight line down to give a strong blow. In total, it can cause `LC, DA, {0:#}` base damage. End the incidental burning effect of the hit area."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_10707	"连续点击技。使用链球不断砸击地面，连续按键可以增加攻击次数，最后一击在地面形成灼烧区域。总共可造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。结束一击区域附带灼烧效果。"	"Continuous click technology. Using hammer to hit the ground continuously can increase the number of attacks, the last hit on the ground to form a burning area. In total, it can cause `LC, DA, {0:#}` base damage. End the incidental burning effect of the hit area."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_10708	"将链球甩出，用力抡起链球，并持续移动，形成大范围的伤害，可以手动控制移动。总共可造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。"	"The hammer is thrown out, the hammer is lifted forcefully, and the hammer is moved continuously, resulting in a wide range of injuries, which can be controlled by hand. In total, it can cause `LC, DA, {0:#}` base damage."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_10709	"从天而降，将链球在地面碾压，对周围敌人造成大量伤害。总共可造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。结束一击区域附带灼烧效果。"	"Down from the sky, the hammer is crushed on the ground, causing a lot of damage to the enemy around. In total, it can cause `LC, DA, {0:#}` base damage. End the incidental burning effect of the hit area."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_10788	向指定方向闪避4米距离。基础闪避能量600点，每次闪避消耗300点。可以通过装备徽章提高闪避能量和回复速度。	"Avoid 4 meters in the specified direction. Base evasion energy is 600 points, each evasion consumes 300 points. Avoidance energy and recovery speed can be increased by equipping badges."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_10801	"使用冰炮连续射击，每个输出循环可造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。"	"With continuous firing of ice cannon, each output cycle can cause `LC, DA, {0:%}` base damage."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_10805	"蓄力技。按住技能按钮可进入冰炮蓄力状态，在前方形成伤害区域，松开按钮发射速冻寒气造成伤害，并将敌人冰冻，蓄力时间越长造成伤害越高，冰冻时间越长。最多可造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。附带冰冻效果。"	"Intensive skill. Press the skill button to enter the ice cannon storage state. In front of the damage area, release the button to launch quick-frozen air to cause damage, and freeze the enemy. The longer the storage time, the higher the damage, the longer the freezing time. At most `LC, DA, {0:#%}` base damage. With the effect of freezing."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_10806	"用冰炮砸击地面，将敌人浮空，然后发射大量雪球弹造成大量伤害，结束一击可将敌人冰冻。可造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。附带冰冻效果。"	"Ice cannons are used to hit the ground, float the enemy, and then launch a large number of snowballs, causing a lot of damage. The end of a blow can freeze the enemy. Can cause `LC, DA, {0:#}` base damage. With the effect of freezing."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_10807	"用冰炮发射一道寒冰光束，对直线上的敌人造成连续不断的伤害，可以手动控制横向移动，最多可造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。"	"Ice cannon fires a beam of ice, causing continuous damage to enemies in a straight line. It can manually control the lateral movement, causing up to `LC, DA, {0:#%}` basic damage."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_10808	"从天而降砸击地面，随后向四周发射大量雪球弹，并将敌人冰冻，可造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。附带冰冻效果。"	"A large number of snowballs are fired from the sky and hit the ground, then freeze the enemy, which can cause `LC, DA, {0:#%}` basic damage. With the effect of freezing."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_10888	向指定方向闪避4米距离。基础闪避能量600点，每次闪避消耗300点。可以通过装备徽章提高闪避能量和回复速度。	"Avoid 4 meters in the specified direction. Base evasion energy is 600 points, each evasion consumes 300 points. Avoidance energy and recovery speed can be increased by equipping badges."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_12001	"使用大刀和电击枪连续攻击，每个输出循环可造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。"	"With a knife and an electric shotgun, each output cycle can cause `LC, DA, {0:#}` base damage."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_12005	"蓄力技。按住技能按钮可进入电击枪蓄力状态，松开按钮发射闪电链造成连锁伤害，蓄力时间越久连锁次数越多，在目标稀少时，同一目标会被多次连锁。同时令目标减速。最多可造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。雷属性：附带减速效果。"	"Intensive skill. Press the skill button to enter the shotgun storage state, release the button to launch the lightning chain to cause chain damage. The longer the storage time, the more chain times. When the target is scarce, the same target will be chain multiple times. At the same time, slow down the target. At most `LC, DA, {0:#%}` base damage. Ray Attribute: Incidental deceleration effect."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_12006	"蓄力技。按住技能按钮可进入球状闪电蓄力状态，松开按钮高速向前冲出，以球状闪电形态，伤害所有接触到的敌人，期间可以手动控制移动方向，蓄力时间越久，球状闪电持续时间越长。最多可造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。"	"Intensive skill. Press the skill button to enter the spherical lightning storage state, release the button to rush forward at high speed, and injure all the enemies in contact with the spherical lightning form, during which the movement direction can be controlled manually. The longer the storage time, the longer the spherical lightning duration. At most `LC, DA, {0:#%}` base damage."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_12007	"钻入地面，在地下形成电场，随后跃出地面，将电流全部释放，可造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。雷属性：附带减速效果。"	"Drilling into the ground, forming an electric field in the ground, then jumping out of the ground, releasing all the current, can cause `LC, DA, {0:#}` basic damage. Ray Attribute: Incidental deceleration effect."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_12008	"召唤一艘幽灵海盗船，对直线上的敌人造成伤害，最多可造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。"	"Call a ghost pirate ship to do damage to enemies in a straight line, which can cause up to `LC, DA, {0:#}` base damage."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_12088	向指定方向闪避4米距离。基础闪避能量600点，每次闪避消耗300点。可以通过装备徽章提高闪避能量和回复速度。	"Avoid 4 meters in the specified direction. Base evasion energy is 600 points, each evasion consumes 300 points. Avoidance energy and recovery speed can be increased by equipping badges."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_12101	"使用毛笔凌空点划，对周围目标连续攻击。每个输出循环可造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。"	"Use the brush to hit the target in succession. Each output cycle can cause `LC, DA, {0:#}` base damage."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_12105	"向正前方释放数条墨龙，击退前方目标。消耗目标800点霸体值，并造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。"	"Release several ink dragons to the front and repel the target ahead. Consumption target 800 hegemony value, and cause `LC, DA, {0:#}` base damage."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_12106	"毛笔虚点，形成墨龙环绕周身，边移动边攻击周围目标。攻击造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。"	"The brush dots, forming the ink dragon around the body, moving while attacking the surrounding targets. Attacks cause `LC, DA, {0:#}` base damage."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_12107	"神龙清官用力使用毛笔搅动地面形成黑色漩涡，将目标吸入其中并进行攻击。攻击造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。"	"Shenlong Qingguan used his brush to agitate the ground to form a black whirlpool, sucking the target in and attacking it. Attacks cause `LC, DA, {0:#}` base damage."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_12108	"神龙清官的令牌化为泰山般大小迅速砸击地面，眩晕并攻击周围目标。可造成`LC,DA,{0:#%}`基础伤害。"	"The Shenlong Qingguan's token changed into a Taishan-like size and quickly hit the ground, dizzying and attacking surrounding targets. Can cause `LC, DA, {0:#}` base damage."
	SKILL_EFFECT_DESC_12188	向指定方向闪避4米距离。基础闪避能量600点，每次闪避消耗300点。可以通过装备徽章提高闪避能量和回复速度。	"Avoid 4 meters in the specified direction. Base evasion energy is 600 points, each evasion consumes 300 points. Avoidance energy and recovery speed can be increased by equipping badges."
	SKILL_TYPE_1	普通攻击	Ordinary Attack
	SKILL_TYPE_2	蓄力技能	Intensive skills
	SKILL_TYPE_3	连点技能	Connection skills
	SKILL_TYPE_4	切换技能	Switching Skills
	SKILL_TYPE_5	闪避技能	Avoidance skills
	SKILL_TYPE_6	普通技能	General Skills
	SKILL_COOLDOWNTIME	冷却时间：	Cooling time:
