#	字典配置表		
#	Key		Value
#	string		string
#	字典主键	策划备注	字典内容，可使用转义符
	PLOTDIALOGUE_NPCNAME_01	亚瑟	Arthur
	PLOTDIALOGUE_NPCNAME_02	荆轲	Jing Ke
	PLOTDIALOGUE_NPCNAME_03	狮心王	Lionheart
	PLOTDIALOGUE_NPCNAME_04	卡特琳娜	Katrina
	PLOTDIALOGUE_NPCNAME_05	梅林	Merlin
	PLOTDIALOGUE_NPCNAME_06	凯撒	Caesar
	PLOTDIALOGUE_NPCNAME_07	黑胡子	Blackbeard
	PLOTDIALOGUE_NPCNAME_08	斯巴达克斯	Spartacus
	PLOTDIALOGUE_NPCNAME_09	冰雪少女	Ice and Snow Girl
	PLOTDIALOGUE_NPCNAME_10	玛丽	Mary
	PLOTDIALOGUE_NPCNAME_11	贞德	Joan of Joan
	PLOTDIALOGUE_NPCNAME_12	杰克	Jack
	PLOTDIALOGUE_NPCNAME_13	达芬奇	Vinci
	PLOTDIALOGUE_NPCNAME_14	范海辛	Van Helsing
	PLOTDIALOGUE_NPCNAME_15	艳后	Yan Hou
	PLOTDIALOGUE_NPCNAME_16	岳飞	Yue Fei
	PLOTDIALOGUE_NPCNAME_17	佐罗	Zorro
	PLOTDIALOGUE_NPCNAME_18	项羽	Xiang Yu
	PLOTDIALOGUE_NPCNAME_19	罗宾汉	Robin Hood
	PLOTDIALOGUE_NPCNAME_20	虞姬	Yu Ji
	PLOTDIALOGUE_NPCNAME_21	时空使	Space-time Cause
	PLOTDIALOGUE_NPCNAME_22	骷髅盾牌兵	Skeleton Shield Soldier
	PLOTDIALOGUE_NPCNAME_23	兰斯洛特	Lancelot
	PLOTDIALOGUE_NPCNAME_24	银甲狼人	Silver Wolf
	PLOTDIALOGUE_NPCNAME_25	熔岩怪	Lava Troll
	PLOTDIALOGUE_NPCNAME_26	双斧兽人	Orc with two axes
	PLOTDIALOGUE_NPCNAME_27	噬魂者灰甲	Soul-eater's Grey Armor
	PLOTDIALOGUE_NPCNAME_29	瘟疫之源	Source of plague
	PLOTDIALOGUE_NPCNAME_30	洛丽塔	Lolita
	PLOTDIALOGUE_NPCNAME_31	伊蕾莎	Elesha
	PLOTDIALOGUE_NPCNAME_99	索尼亚	Sonia
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_1200011	加油！一定不要让我失望哦！	Come on. Don't let me down!
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_1200021	嗯？你这是在哪儿说话的？	Uh huh? Where are you talking?
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_1200031	这点本事没有，还怎么做要塞最高顾问。	"This ability is not there, how to do the fortress Supreme adviser."
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_1200041	还不算是个摆设花瓶…	It's not a vase yet.
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_1200051	可恶！你说什么？	Abhorrent! I beg your pardon?
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_1200061	这额…时间紧迫，我要去完成试炼了。	"Well, time is pressing. I'm going to finish the trial."
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_1200071	当心，双斧兽人就在前方！	"Be careful, the double axe orcs are ahead!"
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_1200081	哼！这种对手可难不倒我！	Hum! This kind of opponent can't beat me!
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_1200091	感受到敌人的气息了。只是…这种程度…	Feel the enemy's breath. It's just... To this extent...
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_1200101	也太弱了点！	It's too weak!
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_1200111	你这鼻子可比那些狼崽子灵多了。	You have a better nose than those wolf pups.
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_1200121	……	...
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_1200131	快要接近银甲狼人了！	Near the Silver Werewolf!
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_1200141	回去告诉达达里奥，银甲狼人什么的再也不会出现了。	Go back and tell Dadario that the Silver Werewolf or something will never appear again.
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_1200151	打都还没打呢！就知道吹牛？	I haven't played yet. You know how to brag?
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_1200161	它已经死了！！！	It's dead!!!
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_1200171	试炼的最后一关咯！击败焰铠卫士后，你就将是光荣的要塞正式成员咯！	"The last pass of the trial! After defeating the guards of the flame armor, you will be a full member of the glorious fortress."
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_1200181	虽然对要塞正式成员没有一点兴趣，但是为了守护那个曾经生活过的家园，也只好先这样了。	"Although not interested in the official members of the fortress, but in order to protect that once lived home, we had to do so first."
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_1200191	虽然总是这副很臭屁的样子，但是不得不说，挺酷的…	"It's always such a stinky look, but I have to say, it's cool."
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_1200201	我们到了！焰铠卫士正是在这儿召唤邪恶生物。	Here we are. It is here that the Fire Armor summons evil creatures.
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_1200211	只要打败它，永夜遗迹是不是就彻底的安宁了？	"If we defeat it, will the remains of Yongye be completely peaceful?"
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_1200221	那可不一定，谁知道它们还有多少后着！	That's not necessarily true. Who knows how many more of them are coming!
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_1200231	兵来将挡水来土掩，先解决了它再说其他！	"Soldiers come to cover up the water and earth, first solve it and then say something else!"
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_1200241	这些怪物到底什么来头，打完一茬又一茬，怎么也割不完！	What are the origins of these monsters? They can't be cut off after they have fought one after another!
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_2200011	这些怪物，说来话长……	These monsters have a long story to tell...
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_2200021	长话短说！	Cut a long story short!
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_2200031	这些怪物，都是受魔神鲁廷加和它的仆从魔化的各个位面的生物。其中，也不乏我们要塞的战友……	"These monsters are all creatures of all planes demonized by the Devil Rutinga and his followers. Among them, there are also comrades in arms who we want to fortify..."
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_2200041	曾经的战友么……	Have you ever been a comrade in arms?
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_2200051	这样的战斗，是不是特别的残酷？	Is such a battle particularly cruel?
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_2200061	那么从今天起！我将再也不允许任何一个战友坠入魔爪！	So from today on! I will never allow any comrade-in-arms to fall into the claws again!
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_2200071	这里太隐蔽了，幸好我们足够细心。死灵将军应该就藏身于这个秘密基地。	"It's too hidden here. Fortunately, we're careful enough. General Necromancer should be hiding in this secret base."
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_2200081	不认真一些，怎么和这些魔物们战斗，又怎么能确保战友们的安全？	"If we don't take it seriously, how can we fight with these demons and ensure the safety of our comrades?"
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_2200091	比起平时吊儿郎当、假装高冷的你，我更喜欢你现在认真愤怒的样子。	I prefer the way you look serious and angry to the way you usually hang around and pretend to be cold.
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_2200101	……	...
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_2200111	卑鄙的邪恶军团。它们再一次成功的惹怒了我！	A despicable army of evil. Once again they succeeded in provoking me!
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_2200121	冷静下来，不要中了它们的诡计。传奇英雄的定力都异于常人，这也是我们选择你的原因。身为传奇英雄的荆轲不会被永远的蛊惑，一定会有解救他的办法。	"Calm down. Don't fall for their tricks. Legendary heroes are different from ordinary people in their determination, which is why we choose you. As a legendary hero, Jing Yi will not be perplexed forever. There must be a way to save him."
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_3210011	希望如此…	I hope so.
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_3210021	总之，先击败魔化后的荆轲，带回去慢慢想办法吧！	"In short, first defeat the demonized Jing Ke, take it back and think slowly!"
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_3210031	我已经能感受到魔化荆轲那强大的力量波动了。果然不愧是传奇英雄！	"I can already feel the fluctuation of the powerful power of the demonized Jing Ke. Sure enough, it's a legendary hero!"
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_4220011	喂！他现在可是魔化状态，这英雄惺惺相惜的戏码恐怕得等到降服他之后才能演哦！	Hello! He's in a demonized state now. I'm afraid that the hero's regretful play can't be performed until he surrenders to him! ____________
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_4220021	能和强大的荆轲战斗，我很满足。	I am satisfied to be able to fight against the powerful Jingke.
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_4220031	这个明奇博士真是让人头痛的家伙。这里还未全面侦查探索过，不知道会不会有敌人存在。	"This Dr. Minch is a real headache. We haven't fully investigated and explored here, and we don't know if there will be enemies."
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_4220041	那就只能紧跟着他，寸步不离了。	That's the only way to keep up with him.
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_4220051	哇！这是新加入队伍的英雄么？希望不要像荆轲那样高冷爱欺负人哦！	WOW! Is this a new hero? I hope you don't bully people like Jing Ke.
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_4220061	……	...
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_4220071	不好！有埋伏！我们被包围了。	Not good! There's an ambush! We were surrounded.
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_4220081	不必紧张，我看星魂碎片一定就在这大块头的手中。	Don't be nervous. I think the ghost debris must be in the hands of this big man.
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_4220091	块头倒是挺大，就是不知道本事是不是和它的块头一样大！	"The head is big, but I don't know if it is as big as its size."
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_4220101	这里的地形有些复杂，注意不要迷路。	The terrain here is somewhat complicated. Be careful not to get lost.
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_30101	时间紧迫，快点出发吧！	Time is pressing. Let's get going.
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_30102	说起利爪狼王，我倒是想起了我试炼时击败的那个银甲狼人。	"Speaking of the Wolf King of Claws, I think of the Silver Wolf I defeated in my trial."
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_30103	银甲狼人被击败之后，邪恶军团利用这里的机械技术对它进行了改造。准确的说，确实是同一个东西。	"After the Silver Werewolf was defeated, the Evil Legion used the mechanical technology here to transform it. It's exactly the same thing."
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_30104	难怪这气息如此的熟悉。	No wonder it smells so familiar.
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_30105	改造过后的狼王今非昔比，一定不能掉以轻心。	"After the transformation, the wolf king is not what it used to be. It must not be taken lightly."
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_30106	能不能快点离开这里，这里七晕八绕的，地方还都长的差不多。我已经分不清东南西北，晕到想吐了。	Can you get out of here quickly? It's all around here. It's about the same length. I can't tell the southeast from the northwest. I feel sick.
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_30107	再忍一忍，总要找到机械迷城的幕后头目。击败它，才能离开。	"If you endure it again, you will always find the leader behind the mechanical maze. Beat it before you leave."
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_30108	来了！熟悉的套路，又是臭鱼烂虾们无能的阴谋诡计。	"Coming! Familiar routines, but also stinky fish, rotten shrimp incompetent schemes."
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_30109	所以说，我们又是被包围了吗？	"So, are we surrounded again?"
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_30201	喂喂！这种事能不能认真点。	Hello! Can you be serious about this kind of thing?
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_30202	明明是个艺术家，现在也要来靠实力战斗了嘛？	"Mingming is an artist, but now we have to rely on strength to fight it?"
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_30203	喂！你这次好像没有之前那么愤怒哦！	Hello! You don't seem as angry as before this time.
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_30204	因为我能打败他，拯救他啊！最终会没事的嘛！	Because I can defeat him and save him! It will be all right in the end.
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_30205	你们说！等达芬奇恢复神智的时候，我可以问他要幅画吗？听说很值钱，卖掉以后岂不是装备随便买，星图任性升？	"You say! When Leonardo regains his sanity, may I ask him if he wants a painting? It's said that it's very valuable. Isn't IT equipment that you buy casually after you sell it, and Star Map is self-willed?"
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_30206	我也要请他帮我画幅画，就画我自己，名字就叫《伊蕾莎》。一定要超越蒙娜丽莎才行！	"I also asked him to help me draw a picture, just draw myself, the name is Eliza. Must surpass the Mona Lisa!"
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_30207	喂喂！现在是众志成城，拯救队友的时刻，你们能不能严肃点？	Hello! Now is the time for all the people to come together and save their teammates. Can you be serious?
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_30208	别说啦！来了来了，达芬奇他来了！	Don't talk about it! Here comes Da Vinci. Here he is!
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_30301	好冷啊这里！能不能找些怪物活动一下手脚，我都快冻僵了。	It's so cold here! Can you find some monsters to move around? I'm freezing.
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_30302	生存在这冰天雪地里，这些怪物，也真是够可怜的。让我们解脱它们吧！	"Living in this ice and snow, these monsters are really poor. Let's get rid of them."
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_30303	霜雪哨站的头领冰甲雪兽就在前方。为了不打草惊蛇，我们需要以迅雷不及掩耳之势解决了它。	"The head of the Frost and Snow Sentinel is in front of the Snow and Ice Beast. In order not to frighten the snake, we need to solve it in a hurry."
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_30304	这种事，就交给我吧！	"This kind of thing, just leave it to me!"
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_30305	为了那些牺牲的同胞们，为了义无反顾的战友们。这次的战斗必须胜利。	"For those who have sacrificed, for those who have never looked back. This battle must be won."
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_30306	看来露娜的游侠团的故事对你的触动很大。瘟疫之源是鲁廷加手下重要的仆从之一。它传播的瘟疫带来死亡，同时被感染的生物会成为死灵生物。消灭它，整个邪恶军团的死灵生物们就只能是一帮乌合之众。	"It seems that the story of Luna's Rangers is very touching to you. The source of the plague was one of Rutinga's important servants. It spreads plagues that cause death, while infected organisms become dead creatures. To eradicate it, the whole evil legion of dead creatures can only be a mob."
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_30401	那还等什么！大局和仇恨都需要我们除掉它，我们要做的就是战斗！	What are we waiting for? The whole situation and hatred need us to get rid of it. All we have to do is fight!
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_30402	冰天雪地也覆盖不了瘟疫之源那腐烂的死亡气息。他就在这里。	Ice and snow can't cover the decaying smell of death at the source of the plague. He's right here.
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_30403	它很有些手段，千万当心！	It has some means. Be careful!
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_30501	为了避开敌人的主力，我们只能选择这陷阱重重的危险绝地。这里的敌人防守力量薄弱很多。但是一定要注意那些陷阱。	"In order to avoid the enemy's main force, we have to choose the dangerous Jedi trapped in this trap. The enemy's defence here is much weaker. But we must pay attention to those pitfalls."
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_30502	放心！即便是和敌人的主力刚正面，我们也不畏惧。更别说这种压力小很多的突袭了，保证完成任务。	"Don't worry! Even if we are in front of the enemy's main force, we are not afraid. Not to mention that the pressure is much less sudden, to ensure the completion of the task."
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_30601	功败垂成，就再此一战。趁着风声走漏之前打败守卫异魔王殿，那这次突袭就完美的成功了。	"If we succeed or fail, we will fight again. The raid was a perfect success, taking advantage of the fact that the guard of the Devil's Palace was defeated before the wind leaked out."
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_30602	看到你这么胸有成竹的样子，恐怕这异魔王殿，你已经吃定了对吧？	"Seeing you look like a bamboo in your chest, I'm afraid you've already eaten the Hall of the Devil King, haven't you?"
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_30603	这种事，嘴巴说没用，得靠拳头。	It's no use talking about this kind of thing. You have to rely on your fists.
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_30604	冰雪少女？一个小萝莉会有什么战斗力呢！	Ice and snow girl? What fighting power does a little Lori have?
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_30605	可不要小瞧她，虽然小巧，人家可是战斗英雄，恐怕不比你差呢！	"But don't underestimate her, although small, people are fighting heroes, I'm afraid not worse than you!"
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_30606	那倒要好好领教领教。	That's a good idea.
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_30607	你又要欺负女孩子了么？	Are you going to bully girls again?
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_30608	……	...
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_30609	冰雪少女！你在哪里？快和姐姐一起回家吧！	Ice and snow girl! Where are you? Come home with your sister!
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_40101	能不能不要大呼小叫，你干脆加入邪恶军团好好和她团聚咯！	Can you just join the evil army and get together with her instead of yelling?
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_40102	哼！你给我记着，人家还小，动手时一定要注意轻重。	"Hum! You remember to me, people are still young, we must pay attention to the importance of starting."
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_40103	这里估计十有八九已经是被魔王控制了，我们进去还是谨慎些为好。	"It is estimated that in nine cases out of ten, the devil has taken control of it. It is better for us to be cautious when we go in."
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_40104	不愧是时空魔王，这里的零部件都被他用魔法组合成魔鬼机械兵，看来咱们后面的路不会很轻松。	The devil of time and space is worthy of it. The parts and components here are combined by magic into devil mechanics. It seems that the road behind us will not be easy.
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_40105	不管如何，一定要把人救出来。	"Anyway, we must save people."
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_40201	这里又是这么安静…好想回家…我…我还是个女孩纸…	It's so quiet here again. I want to go home. I... I'm still a girl.
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_40202	……	...
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_40203	太闹腾了，转世后连性格都变了。	It's too noisy. Even personality changes after reincarnation.
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_40204	再转世我也是女孩子，你就不能温柔点，再说…我还是时空管理员呢…你就不能对我客气嘛。	"I'm a girl again, so you can't be gentle. I'm still a space-time administrator. You can't be polite to me."
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_40205	好好，真服了你了。跟紧点，别一会儿把你丢了。	"Okay, I really obeyed you. Come on, don't lose you in a minute."
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_40206	这里除了机械兵外，还有冥界的妖兽，看来这次时空魔王的魔力已经强大到可以从冥界召唤妖兽了。	"In addition to the mechanics, there are also monsters in the underworld. It seems that the magic of the time and space monsters has become so powerful that they can summon monsters from the underworld."
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_40207	冥界…千年前他的能力还不能达到哪里…	"Underworld... Thousands of years ago, his abilities could not be achieved."
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_40208	看来这次时空魔王不是一般的强大。	It seems that this time the Devil of Time and Space is not generally strong.
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_40401	等等，我在这里感受的了一股非常危险的气氛。	Wait a minute. I feel a very dangerous atmosphere here.
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_40402	难道这里有冥界的生物…	Are there creatures in the underworld?
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_40403	冥界的妖兽还真不是一般的难对付…不知道魔王这次召唤了多少冥界妖兽。	The monsters of the underworld are not so hard to deal with. I don't know how many monsters the Devil King summoned this time.
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_40404	不管魔王召唤多少，我们只能走一步看一步了。	"No matter how much the devil calls, we can only take one step at a time."
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_40601	为什么我来到这里有一种莫名的不安？	Why do I come here with an inexplicable uneasiness?
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_40602	又有冥兽了？	Hades again?
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_40603	不对，这里有时空英雄能量的波动，难道这里有被魔幻的时空英雄…	"No, there are fluctuations in the energy of space-time heroes. Are there magical space-time heroes here?"
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_40604	宝贝们，你们都是来找我画微笑的嘛？来来来，我帮你们画脸…	"Baby, are you all coming to me to draw a smile? Come on, I'll draw your faces."
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_40605	达芬奇…	Leonardo Da Vinci...
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_40606	魔王说会给我永恒的生命的，你们不会理解死去一千多年的寂寞，我还有很多事情没有搞清楚，等待我发现…是我拯救了人类…是我…	"The Devil King said that he would give me eternal life. You will not understand the loneliness of dying for more than a thousand years. I still have many things not clear up, waiting for me to find out. I saved the human race. It's me."
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_40607	叛徒，我以为你是被魔幻了，没想到你是真心叛变！	"Traitor, I thought you were magic, but I didn't think you were really mutinous!"
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_40608	跟他废什么话，干掉他…	What nonsense do you have with him? Kill him.
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_40609	你们太弱，我…会再来找你们的…嘿嘿…	"You are too weak, I... I'll come back to you. Hey hey..."
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_40610	该死，让他跑掉了…	"Damn it, let him run away."
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_40611	没关系，以后一定还会遇到他。	Never mind. I'll meet him again in the future.
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_50101	索尼亚，从达芬奇那里搜出的线索说的是这里吗？	"Sonia, is that what the clue from Leonardo Da Vinci says?"
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_50102	嗯，线索说的的确是这里，不过…好冷啊……	"Well, the clue is really here, but... It's so cold..."
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_50103	空气很冷，但杀气很重，不过…我就喜欢种嗜血的气氛。	"The air is cold, but it is very hard to kill, but... I like to grow a bloodthirsty atmosphere."
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_50104	这些冰属性的怪物的确有些实力，不过时空魔王手下的暗系黑暗法师瘟疫之源才是冰封地狱中最可怕的。	"These ice-attributed monsters do have some strength, but the source of the plague of the Dark Master under the Devil of Time and Space is the most terrible in the frozen hell."
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_50105	瘟疫之源我有印象，上一次封印之战时咱们时空英雄中就有几人不幸死在他的瘟疫攻击中，这次要是再碰上咱们可要小心啊。	I am impressed by the source of plague. Several of our time and space heroes died in his plague attack during the last Seal War. We should be careful if we meet again this time.
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_50301	这里好浓的瘴气，空气中到处都是死亡的气息。	There's a lot of lameness and death in the air.
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_50302	来了3个小家伙，嘿嘿…	"Here come three little guys, hey hey"
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_50303	满满的生机，满满的生机，你们将与我的瘴气融合化为魔气成为可以强大我的力量，哈哈哈……	"Full of life, full of life, you will fuse my lameness into magic gas to become a powerful force for me, ha ha ha..."
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_50304	瘟疫之源…	The source of plague.
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_50305	瘟疫之源的病毒攻击果然厉害，要不是我躲的快，恐怕刚才…	"The source of the plague virus attack is indeed severe, if I did not hide quickly, I am afraid that just now.."
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_50306	斯巴达克斯…我…好像…	Spartacus... I... It seems that...
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_50307	索尼亚…，索尼亚…	Sonia... Sonia...
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_50401	该死的瘟疫之源，我们竟然没有注意到他攻击了索尼亚，如果索尼亚出什么事你可别指望咱俩能阻止时空魔王。	"We didn't even notice that he attacked Sonia at the source of the damn plague. If something happens to Sonia, you can't expect us to stop the Devil of Time and Space."
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_50402	咱们要尽快找到解毒药才行。现在陷阱约来越多，咱们要多注意了。	"Let's find the antidote as soon as possible. Now the more traps we have, the more attention we should pay to them."
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_50601	斯巴达克斯，你有没有头晕的感觉，我动作越来越僵硬。	"Spartacus, do you feel dizzy? I'm getting more and more stiff."
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_50602	原来你也感受到了，我以为是杀怪累到了。	So you feel it too. I thought it was killing monsters and getting tired.
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_50603	这个应该是控制咱们时空英雄魔法的波动，没想到这里竟然有被捆的时空英雄。	"This is supposed to control the fluctuation of our time and space heroic magic, unexpectedly there are bound time and space heroes here."
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_50604	自相残杀的感受真不好，时空魔王简直太卑鄙了。	It's a bad feeling to kill each other. The Devil of Time and Space is so despicable.
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_50605	终于有人来陪我玩了，来啊，快来陪我啊，嘻嘻嘻~~~	Finally someone came to play with me. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on.~~~
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_50606	斯巴达克斯，没想到我们会…会已这种方式碰面，谢谢你们救了我。	"Spartacus, I didn't expect that we would... I'll meet you this way. Thank you for saving me."
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_50607	洛丽塔，现在索尼亚中毒需要解药，你知道哪里可以找到吗？	"Lolita, now Sonia poisoning needs antidote. Do you know where to find it?"
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_50608	解药在死亡城堡中地狱男爵的手里，我没法弄到。	The antidote is in the hands of the Hellboy in the Castle of Death. I can't get it.
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_50609	地狱男爵…	Hellboy...
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_50610	好，洛丽塔我们先带你回城休息，然后前往死亡城堡。	"Okay, Lolita, let's take you back to the city for a rest and then to the castle of death."
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_50611	这里好浓的瘴气，空气中到处都是死亡的气息。	There's a lot of lameness and death in the air.
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_50612	来了3个小家伙，嘿嘿…	"Here come three little guys, hey hey"
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_50613	满满的生机，满满的生机，你们将与我的瘴气融合化为魔气成为可以强大我的力量，哈哈哈……	"Full of life, full of life, you will fuse my lameness into magic gas to become a powerful force for me, ha ha ha..."
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_50614	瘟疫之源…	The source of plague.
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_50615	瘟疫之源的病毒攻击果然厉害，要不是我躲的快，恐怕刚才…	"The source of the plague virus attack is indeed severe, if I did not hide quickly, I am afraid that just now.."
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_50616	斯巴达克斯…我…好像…	Spartacus... I... It seems that...
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_50617	索尼亚…，索尼亚…	Sonia... Sonia...
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_50618	该死的瘟疫之源，我们竟然没有注意到他攻击了索尼亚，如果索尼亚出什么事你可别指望咱俩能阻止时空魔王。	"We didn't even notice that he attacked Sonia at the source of the damn plague. If something happens to Sonia, you can't expect us to stop the Devil of Time and Space."
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_50619	咱们要尽快找到解毒药才行。现在陷阱约来越多，咱们要多注意了。	"Let's find the antidote as soon as possible. Now the more traps we have, the more attention we should pay to them."
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_50620	斯巴达克斯，你有没有头晕的感觉，我动作越来越僵硬。	"Spartacus, do you feel dizzy? I'm getting more and more stiff."
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_50621	原来你也感受到了，我以为是杀怪累到了。	So you feel it too. I thought it was killing monsters and getting tired.
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_50622	这个应该是控制咱们时空英雄魔法的波动，没想到这里竟然有被捆的时空英雄。	"This is supposed to control the fluctuation of our time and space heroic magic, unexpectedly there are bound time and space heroes here."
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_50623	自相残杀的感受真不好，时空魔王简直太卑鄙了。	It's a bad feeling to kill each other. The Devil of Time and Space is so despicable.
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_50624	终于有人来陪我玩了，来啊，快来陪我啊，嘻嘻嘻~~~	Finally someone came to play with me. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on.~~~
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_50625	斯巴达克斯，没想到我们会…会已这种方式碰面，谢谢你们救了我。	"Spartacus, I didn't expect that we would... I'll meet you this way. Thank you for saving me."
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_50626	洛丽塔，现在索尼亚中毒需要解药，你知道哪里可以找到吗？	"Lolita, now Sonia poisoning needs antidote. Do you know where to find it?"
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_50627	解药在死亡城堡中地狱男爵的手里，我没法弄到。	The antidote is in the hands of the Hellboy in the Castle of Death. I can't get it.
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_50628	地狱男爵…	Hellboy...
	PLOTDIALOGUE_TALK_50629	好，洛丽塔我们先带你回城休息，然后前往死亡城堡。	"Okay, Lolita, let's take you back to the city for a rest and then to the castle of death."
#	任务对话		
	TASK_TALK_1	欢迎来到风暴要塞！	Welcome to Storm Fortress!
	TASK_TALK_2	我是伊蕾莎！将是你最贴心的顾问。	I'm Eliza! It will be your most intimate advisor.
	TASK_TALK_3	要塞指挥官科斯塔。他等你很久了，去和他聊聊吧！	Fortress Commander Costa. He has been waiting for you for a long time. Go and talk to him.
	TASK_TALK_4	欢迎来到风暴要塞！风暴要塞建立在虚空风暴的边缘。目的是为了抵抗上古魔神鲁廷加的入侵，让我们共同的家园远离战火。	"Welcome to Storm Fortress! Storm fortresses are built on the edge of empty storms. The purpose is to resist the invasion of Rutinga, the ancient demon god, and to keep our common home away from the war."
	TASK_TALK_5	为了实现这样伟大的目标，我们召唤来曾经在历史上留下璀璨传说的家伙。你！就是其中之一！	"In order to achieve such a great goal, we call upon the people who once left a brilliant legend in history. You! That's one of them!"
	TASK_TALK_6	今时不同往日。为了证明你可以适应不同时空位面的战斗，我们准备了一些试炼。	"Today is different from the past. In order to prove that you can adapt to the battle of different space-time planes, we have prepared some trials."
	TASK_TALK_7	在离要塞不远的“永夜遗迹-试炼丛林”，散落着一些地精和半兽人。它们统一听从双斧兽人的指挥。去击败它，完成试炼。	"Near the fortress, there are some goblins and orcs scattered in the ""Eternal Night Heritage - Trial Jungle"". They are united under the command of the two-axed orcs. To defeat it, to complete the trial."
	TASK_TALK_8	果然跟传说中的一样厉害呢！但你要以为试炼程度到此为止，那可就大错特错了。	"Sure enough, it's as powerful as the legend! But if you think that the level of trial is up to this point, it's a big mistake."
	TASK_TALK_9	去找到达达里奥，他会给安排新的试炼。	"To find Dadario, he will arrange a new trial."
	TASK_TALK_10	你知道我们这些商人总是要走南闯北，跋山涉水的。	"You know, we businessmen always have to go south, north, mountains and rivers."
	TASK_TALK_11	永夜遗迹一直是最可靠的歇脚点和中转站。但是最近那里变得一点也不安全了，银甲狼人带着狼崽子霸占了那里。	"Yongye remains have always been the most reliable stop and transit station. But lately, it's not safe at all. Silver-armoured werewolves and wolf pups occupy it."
	TASK_TALK_12	请务必将“永夜遗迹-试炼山谷”里令人憎恶的狼崽子们清剿干净。祝你好运！	Be sure to clean up the abominable wolf pups in the "Eternal Night Heritage - Trial Valley". Good luck!
	TASK_TALK_13	干的不错！你离通过试炼只有一步之遥。	Good job! You are only one step away from passing the test.
	TASK_TALK_14	伊蕾莎会为你准备最终的试炼。	Eliza will prepare you for the final trial.
	TASK_TALK_15	据我所知，焰铠卫士在“永夜遗迹-试炼祭坛”召唤邪恶生物来扩充实力。	"As far as I know, the guards of flame armor summon evil creatures to expand their strength in the ""Eternal Night Heritage - Trial Altar""."
	TASK_TALK_16	要想彻底的让永夜遗迹回归安宁，一定要除掉负责召唤的焰铠卫士。	"In order to restore the ruins of Yongnights to peace, we must remove the guards responsible for summoning the flame armor."
	TASK_TALK_17	敌人越来越难对付，但你也在不断的变强哦！	"The enemy is becoming more and more difficult to deal with, but you are also growing stronger!"
	TASK_TALK_18	想体验一下变强后的感觉吗？	Want to experience how it feels when it gets stronger?
	TASK_TALK_19	去找游侠露娜，她知道哪里有更厉害的家伙让你练手。	Go to Ranger Luna. She knows where there are more powerful guys to train you.
	TASK_TALK_20	你能通过试炼来到这里一点儿都没让我感到意外。但是接下来，我会让你知难而退。	"It doesn't surprise me that you can come here through trial. But next, I'll let you back off."
	TASK_TALK_21	在永夜遗迹召唤邪恶生物的可远不止焰铠卫士一个。据我的游侠团调查得知，死灵重拳正在“永夜遗迹-邪恶祭坛”做同样的事。	"It is far more than a guardian of flame that invokes evil creatures in the ruins of eternal night. According to my Rangers'investigation, Dead Heavy Boxing is doing the same thing in the ""Eternal Night Relics - Evil Altar""."
	TASK_TALK_22	灾难还远没有结束。你最好能快点解决死灵重拳。	The disaster is far from over. You'd better get rid of Dead Spirit's Fist sooner.
	TASK_TALK_23	哼！侥幸让你通过了！	Hum! Luckily let you through!
	TASK_TALK_24	告诉伊蕾莎，如果有下一次，我一定不会手下留情。	"Tell Eliza that if there's another time, I won't be merciful."
	TASK_TALK_25	果然只有不断变强，才能应对更棘手的敌人呢！	"Sure enough, only by growing stronger, can we deal with more difficult enemies!"
	TASK_TALK_26	现在，跟我一起学习怎样给英雄升阶吧！	"Now, learn with me how to promote heroes."
	TASK_TALK_27	邪恶军团企图占领永夜遗迹，以之为跳板进攻要塞。幸亏你干脆利落的粉碎了他们的计划。但是，似乎还残留着厉害的家伙我们没有发现…	"The Evil Legion attempted to capture the remains of Yongye as a springboard to attack the fortress. Thank you for crushing their plans. But there seems to be a lot of guys left, and we haven't found them yet."
	TASK_TALK_28	先知法奇奥能预知一些未知的东西。他或许可以告诉你，那躲在黑暗里的敌人究竟在哪！	The prophet Facchio could predict something unknown. He may tell you where the enemy hiding in the dark is!
	TASK_TALK_29	我有些不妙的预感。那些邪恶生物召唤的并不是普通的鲁廷加爪牙，而是……	"I have some bad feelings. Those evil creatures call not ordinary Rutin's jaws, but..."
	TASK_TALK_30	天呐！它们居然召唤了荆轲，一个被杀戮与毁灭蒙蔽了心智和意识的荆轲。去阻止他！他就在“永夜遗迹：终结峡谷”！	"God! They actually called Jing Ke, a Jing Ke whose mind and consciousness were blinded by killing and destruction. Stop him! He's in ""Everlasting Night Heritage: Ending the Canyon""!"
	TASK_TALK_31	真是没有想到，鲁廷加居然用我们的办法来反制我们……	It is unexpected that Rutinga should use our methods to counter us...
	TASK_TALK_32	那些被邪恶侵蚀和蛊惑的异次元的英雄们，天知道还有多少。愿女神保佑他们！	God knows how many heroes of different dimensions are eroded and bewitched by evil. God bless them!
	TASK_TALK_33	永夜遗迹的事情暂且告一段落。要塞的侦察兵发现了一个充满机械科技的位面，我们称之为“机械迷城”。	"Let's call it a day. The reconnaissance of the fortress found a plane full of mechanical technology, which we call the ""Mechanical Maze""."
	TASK_TALK_34	不巧的是，明奇博士听说了之后特别感兴趣。他一定要亲自前往“机械迷城-岗哨前沿”去调查一番。只能委托你保护他的安危。	"Unfortunately, Dr. Minch was particularly interested when he heard about it. He must go to the ""Mechanical Maze - Sentinel Front"" to investigate in person. You can only be entrusted with protecting his safety."
	TASK_TALK_35	幸好有你保护明奇博士。没想到，机械迷城也被邪恶军团侵占了。难道他们又想在机械城召唤英雄？！	"Fortunately, you protected Dr. Minch. Unexpectedly, the mechanical maze was also occupied by the evil army. Do they want to call heroes in Mechanic City?!"
	TASK_TALK_36	等一等，你手上的这个东西是?！星魂碎片！？女神保佑，我们终于找到星魂碎片的踪迹了。	"Wait a minute. What's this thing in your hand?! Star Spirit Fragments!? Goddess bless, we finally found the trace of the soul debris."
	TASK_TALK_37	星魂碎片蕴含的能量对我们很有帮助。占星师凯瑟琳对于星魂碎片有很深的研究，或许她能用的上碎片。	The energy contained in the Star-Spirit debris is very helpful to us. Astrologer Catherine has a deep understanding of ghost debris. Maybe she can use it.
	TASK_TALK_38	我一直在尝试研究一套激活系统去激发星魂碎片所蕴藏着的巨大能量，我称它为“星图”。	"I've been trying to develop an activation system to stimulate the enormous energy contained in the ghost debris, which I call the Star Map."
	TASK_TALK_39	之前从没有一片真正的星魂碎片能验证它是否正常，直到你带来了这枚碎片。现在，让我们一起去验证一下吧！	There was never a real piece of ghost debris to verify that it was normal until you brought it. Now let's verify it together.
	TASK_TALK_40	成功了！效果比我想象中的还要好，之后再得到所有的“星魂碎片”我们都可以派上大用场了……	"Succeed! The effect is better than I expected, and then we can use all the ""Star and Spirit Fragments""..."
	TASK_TALK_41	只不过，我们千辛万苦的寻找，都没有发现它的踪迹。为什么它会出现在“机械迷城”？	"However, we have worked hard to find it, did not find its trace. Why does it appear in the ""Mechanical Maze""?"
	TASK_TALK_42	有关于星魂碎片的故事，你应该问一下伊蕾莎，没有人比她更清楚了。	You should ask Eliza about the story of the Star Spirit Fragments. No one knows better than her.
	TASK_TALK_43	看来，是时候告诉你“星魂碎片”的事情了。	It seems that it's time to tell you about the "Star and Soul Fragments".
	TASK_TALK_44	在封印鲁廷加的战斗中，女神伊娃耗尽所有神力，陷入沉睡状态。连她的神器“星魂神杖”，也被鲁廷加击碎，随着虚空漩涡被席卷到各个时空位面。	"In the battle to seal Rutinga, Eva exhausted all her powers and fell asleep. Even her artifact, the Star Spirit Scepter, was smashed by Rutinga, and with the Void Vortex swept across all space-time planes."
	TASK_TALK_45	神杖是由我们的星球的星核之力幻化而成，蕴含着几乎一半的星核力量。即便是化为碎片，每一片也都是力量的结晶。	"The wand is a hallucination of the nuclear power of our planet, containing almost half of its nuclear power. Every piece is the crystallization of power, even if it is turned into fragments."
	TASK_TALK_46	自从鲁廷加被封印后，就一直千方百计想要突破封印。它盯上了星魂碎片，吞噬碎片从而获得打破封印的力量。我们，一定不能让它们得逞！	"Since Rutinga was sealed, he has tried every means to break through the seal. It stares at the debris of the Star and devours the debris to gain the power to break the seal. We must not let them succeed!"
	TASK_TALK_47	我们，一定不能让它们得逞！请立即前往“机械迷城-浮空飞船”，寻找其他的碎片。	We must not let them succeed! Please go to "Mechanical Maze - Aerospace Spacecraft" immediately to find other debris.
	TASK_TALK_48	你做的很对。只有集结更多英雄们的力量，才具备跟邪恶军团战斗的资本。	You did it right. Only by assembling the strength of more heroes can we have the capital to fight against the evil army.
	TASK_TALK_49	但是怎么和他们处理好关系，可是一门学问。	But how to deal with them is a learning.
	TASK_TALK_50	先知法奇奥就是个温文尔雅，充满人格魅力的老师。去请教一下他吧。	The Prophet Fachio was a gentle and charming teacher. Go and consult him.
	TASK_TALK_51	人际关系？这东西刻意不得。只要真诚待人，日积月累之下，总会被别人认可的。	"Interpersonal relationship? This thing is deliberate. As long as you treat people sincerely, you will always be recognized by others over the years."
	TASK_TALK_52	不如，现在就跟我一起去帮你的好友做些什么？	Why don't you come with me now and help your friends?
	TASK_TALK_53	你看，其实这一切很简单。重视每一件能关心到别人的小事，他们总会感受到你的诚意的。	"You see, it's all very simple. Pay attention to every little thing that can care about others, they will always feel your sincerity."
	TASK_TALK_54	科斯塔好像正等着你回复他关于星魂碎片的事情，不要让他等太久。	Costa seems to be waiting for you to reply to his story about the ghost debris. Don't let him wait too long.
	TASK_TALK_55	天啦！你们居然成功的激活了星魂碎片的能量。看来机械迷城还蕴藏着更多的碎片，难怪它们连利爪狼王也派了出来。	God! You have succeeded in activating the energies of the Star-Spirit Fragments. It seems that the mechanical maze still contains more debris. No wonder they even sent out the Wolf King of Claws.
	TASK_TALK_56	它就镇守着“机械迷城-锻造平台”，只有通过了它的封锁，才有可能获得更多的碎片。	It guards the "Mechanical Maze - Forging Platform" and only through its blockade can it get more debris.
	TASK_TALK_57	你果然没有让大家失望。那么，这次一定收获颇丰吧！	"You did not disappoint everyone. Well, this must be a good harvest!"
	TASK_TALK_58	为了强化装备，强化星图。金币的消耗一定很大！	"In order to strengthen equipment, strengthen the star map. The consumption of gold coins must be great!"
	TASK_TALK_59	或许我应该告诉你，金币可以使用钻石购买。	Maybe I should tell you that gold coins can be purchased with diamonds.
	TASK_TALK_60	哇哦！又到了提升战力的时刻咯！	Wow! It's time to improve our combat effectiveness again!
	TASK_TALK_61	经过一系列的战斗，已经可以尝试给英雄们升阶了。	"After a series of battles, we can try to elevate our heroes."
	TASK_TALK_62	去试试给英雄升阶吧！	Let's try to elevate our heroes.
	TASK_TALK_63	为了守护要塞，守卫家园。不断的战斗，不断的突破变强。	"In order to guard the fortress, guard the home. Continuous fighting, continuous breakthroughs become stronger."
	TASK_TALK_64	这样的你。真的好让人着迷啊！	You like that. How fascinating!
	TASK_TALK_65	咳咳！下一步就让我们搜索“机械迷城-齿轮大厅”吧！	"Cough! Next, let's search for ""Mechanical Maze - Gear Hall""."
	TASK_TALK_66	整个机械迷城都探索过了。不知道剩下的“星魂碎片”会散落在哪里。	The whole mechanical maze has been explored. I don't know where the rest of the "ghost fragments" will be scattered.
	TASK_TALK_67	竞技大师亚历克斯之前特意来嘱咐过，让你去和他聊聊。	Competitive master Alex had come to ask you to talk to him.
	TASK_TALK_68	有个不好的消息需要通知你。邪恶军团故技重施，再一次召唤了英雄来对付我们。这一次是达芬奇！他们甚至利用蒸汽技术对他进行了改造。	"I have some bad news to inform you. Once again, the Evil Legion has summoned heroes to deal with us. This time it's Leonardo Da Vinci! They even used steam technology to transform him."
	TASK_TALK_69	我们绝不能容忍任何一个同伴遭到如此的毒手。你必须击败他，但却不能伤害他的性命。可能会有些困难，但是，要塞也只能依靠你了！	"We must not tolerate any companion being so poisoned. You have to beat him, but you can't hurt his life. It may be difficult, but the fortress can only depend on you!"
	TASK_TALK_70	我听说了达芬奇的事…这种事情，以后一定还会经常出现。所以，你需要做好心理准备。	I heard about Leonardo Da Vinci. This kind of thing will always happen in the future. So you need to be psychologically prepared.
	TASK_TALK_71	总是这样被动防守太让人窝火了，或许我们应该主动点。	Always passive defense is too popular. Maybe we should take the initiative.
	TASK_TALK_72	侦察兵们在“埋骨冰原”发现了邪恶生物的一处据点，他们利用着恶劣的环境悄悄的扩大着实力。	"The scouts found a stronghold of evil creatures in the ""buried ice sheet"", and they used the harsh environment to quietly expand their strength."
	TASK_TALK_73	或许，我们的第一次出击就应该以它为目标。告诉那些混账们，我们可不是好惹的！	"Maybe our first attack should be aimed at it. Tell those bastards, we're not easy to mess with!"
	TASK_TALK_74	就从最外围的“埋骨冰原-霜雪哨站”开始吧！打他们个出其不意。	Let's start with the outermost "Bone-Burying Ice Field-Frost and Snow Sentinel"! They were hit unexpectedly.
	TASK_TALK_75	哈哈！你的手脚很干净，埋骨冰原的怪物们并不知道大难即将来临。在继续之前，或许你该去见一见亚历克斯。	"Ha-ha! Your hands and feet are clean, and the monsters buried in the ice sheet don't know that the disaster is coming. Maybe you should meet Alex before you go on."
	TASK_TALK_76	为了提升要塞的战斗力。亚历克斯总会组织一些竞技比赛。这不，这次他组织的全要塞英雄们都会参加的排位赛就要开始了。	"In order to enhance the fighting capacity of the fortress. Alex always organizes some competitions. No, the qualifying tournament that he organized for all the heroes of the fortress is about to begin."
	TASK_TALK_77	他了解你的战斗力。所以极力要求我推荐你去参加。	He knows your fighting power. So I strongly ask you to recommend you to attend.
	TASK_TALK_78	来的正好。排位赛马上就要开始了。	It just happened. Qualification is about to begin.
	TASK_TALK_79	要塞为了组织这样的比赛，可是投入了很多物资奖励。	"In order to organize such a competition, the fortress invested a lot of material rewards."
	TASK_TALK_80	拿出你们真正的实力，去获得一个好名次吧！	Take out your real strength and get a good place.
	TASK_TALK_81	露娜刚刚来找过你，她似乎有什么心事。	Luna has just come to see you. She seems to have something on her mind.
	TASK_TALK_82	你一定能帮助到她。	You can certainly help her.
	TASK_TALK_83	我得知你将要与“埋骨冰原-冰覆沉船”的瘟疫之源战斗。	I've learned that you're going to fight the plague of "Bone-Buried Ice Sheet-Ice Sunken Ship".
	TASK_TALK_84	我的游侠团曾经侦查过那里，但是却不幸被瘟疫之源突袭。游侠团的兄弟姐妹损失过半。其中，就以它残害的游侠最多。	"My Rangers had been there, but unfortunately they were attacked by the source of the plague. The brothers and sisters of the Rangers lost more than half of their lives. Among them, it is the most mutilated knight-errant."
	TASK_TALK_85	请原谅我之前的无礼。只希望你能在“埋骨冰原-冰覆沉船”中消灭冰咒巫师，为牺牲在它手下的游侠们报仇。	Please forgive my previous rudeness. I only hope you can wipe out the ice curse wizard in the "Bone-buried Ice Plate-Ice-covered Sunken Ship" and revenge the knights who sacrificed under it.
	TASK_TALK_86	不要小觑它的实力，去消灭它之前，我建议你们至少将队伍英雄人数扩充到三个。	"Don't underestimate its strength. Before destroying it, I suggest you expand the number of heroes to at least three."
	TASK_TALK_87	非常感谢。我想，那些为了要塞丧生在各个位面的游侠们都会得到安息。	Thank you very much. I think that all the knights who died for the fortress will be rested in peace.
	TASK_TALK_88	科斯塔正有些战斗计划等待实施，不要让他等的太久了。	Costa is waiting for some battle plans. Don't let him wait too long.
	TASK_TALK_89	我听说了露娜的事情。为了整个要塞，为了我们的家园。这些牺牲都将会被所有人铭记。	"I heard about Luna. For the whole fortress, for our homeland. These sacrifices will be remembered by all."
	TASK_TALK_90	埋骨冰原的敌人终于发现了我们的进攻。他们加固了防守，现在想要正面突破极不理智。“埋骨冰原-陷阱危地”布满了天然的冰霜陷阱。	"The enemies of the ice sheet finally found our attack. They have strengthened their defence, and it's very unreasonable for them to make a positive breakthrough now. ""Bone-burying ice sheet-trap dangerous land"" is full of natural ice traps."
	TASK_TALK_91	这是他们天然的保护屏障，所以那里的防守非常的薄弱。这恰恰是我们的机会。只要躲避过那些陷阱，我们就能深入腹地。	"This is their natural protective barrier, so the defense there is very weak. This is our chance. As long as we avoid those traps, we can go deep into the hinterland."
	TASK_TALK_92	米雅琪发现了一些很有意思的位面。那些地方是磨炼实力的最佳去处。	Miaki found some interesting planes. Those places are the best places to hone strength.
	TASK_TALK_93	已经有大批如你一样的英雄们都已经尝试挑战，并受益匪浅。	There are already a large number of heroes like you who have tried to challenge and benefited a lot.
	TASK_TALK_94	还等什么呢？赶紧过去吧！晚了可就没位置了。	"What are we waiting for? Let's go! Late, but no place."
	TASK_TALK_95	要知道，你现在的实力对要塞可真是太重要了。	"You know, your strength is really important to the fortress."
	TASK_TALK_96	你终于来了！幸好科斯塔嘱咐我为你留好了位置……	You're here at last! Fortunately Costa told me to reserve a place for you...
	TASK_TALK_97	准备好了吗？那就让我们开始吧！	Are you ready? Let's get started.
	TASK_TALK_98	收获很丰盛哦！只是短短的时间，就能明显的感觉到你们变得更强了。	"The harvest is very rich! In just a short time, you can clearly feel that you have become stronger."
	TASK_TALK_99	不过惊喜还在后面。	But the surprise is still ahead.
	TASK_TALK_100	除了经验副本，还有一处能获得大量金币的位面，金币副本，也马上就要开发了。	"In addition to the experience Instance, there is also a place where a large number of gold coins can be obtained. The gold coin Instance will soon be developed."
	TASK_TALK_101	不要太贪心哦！挑战完之后就直接去找达达里奥吧！他有一笔生意要和你们做。	Don't be too greedy! Go straight to Dadario after the challenge is over. He has a business to do with you.
	TASK_TALK_102	有人花了大价钱，要求消灭“埋骨冰原-巨龙骸骨”中的弑神者。	Someone has spent a lot of money demanding the elimination of the god-killers in the "bone-burying ice sheet-giant dragon skeleton".
	TASK_TALK_103	我知道你正准备前往那里战斗，相信你一定乐意帮我这个忙。事成之后，我会付你足够诚意的报酬。	"I know you're going to fight there, and I'm sure you'll be happy to help me. After that, I'll pay you enough in good faith."
	TASK_TALK_104	合作愉快！相信将来我们还会有很多生意可以做。	A pleasant cooperation I believe we will have a lot of business to do in the future.
	TASK_TALK_105	我可不敢占用你太长时间，伊蕾莎正在四处找你。	I dare not take up too long. Eliza is looking for you everywhere.
	TASK_TALK_106	不是我嫉妒，那小丫头对你可真不一般。难道是喜欢上了你？	It's not that I'm jealous. That little girl is really different to you. Did you fall in love with you?
	TASK_TALK_107	喂喂！你好久都没有来找过我咯！是不是现在变得厉害了，就不再需要伦家了呢？	"Hello! You haven't come to me for a long time! Is it true that now that it's getting worse, there's no need for the Lunjia family anymore?"
	TASK_TALK_108	咳咳！不说这些，有正事要和你说。埋骨冰原的敌人们知道大势已去，它们在“埋骨冰原-雪峰峭壁”集结，并留下了精锐力量掩护撤离。。	Cough! Don't say that. I have something to tell you. The enemies of the buried ice sheet know that the situation is over. They gather in the "buried ice sheet - snow peak cliff" and leave behind the elite force to cover the evacuation.
	TASK_TALK_109	如果我没有猜错的话，按照它们一贯的作风，恐怕又会召唤蛊惑一些棘手的英雄与我们为敌。	"If I am not mistaken, in accordance with their usual style, I am afraid they will call on some difficult heroes to confront us."
	TASK_TALK_110	去毁掉它们的撤退计划！但如果真的遇到了被蛊惑的英雄，第一目标就改为击败并带回他。	"Get rid of their evacuation plans! But if you do encounter a hero who has been deluded, the first goal is to defeat him and bring him back."
	TASK_TALK_111	真没想到，冰雪少女竟然是个可爱的小萝莉！她那么萌，邪恶军团怎么忍心对她下手呢？	"What a surprise, the ice and snow girl is a lovely little Lori! How could the Evil Legion have the heart to attack her when she was so rude?"
	TASK_TALK_112	哼！请你一定要变得更强，好好教训那些混蛋们！	Hum! Please be stronger and teach those bastards a lesson!
	TASK_TALK_113	说到变强，我们似乎有足够的材料去给英雄们升星了。跟我一起去学习一下吧！	"Speaking of becoming stronger, we seem to have enough material to raise stars for heroes. Come and study with me!"
	TASK_TALK_114	我想，如今要塞的实力已经足够支持我们发动一场远征了。就让我们进攻他们的腹地——荷鲁斯神庙吧！	"I think the fortress is strong enough now to support us in launching an expedition. Let's attack their hinterland, the Temple of Horus."
	TASK_TALK_115	那里是鲁廷加爪牙的重要据点，由鲁廷加的忠实奴仆堕落天使镇守。	"It was an important stronghold of Rutinga's jaws, guarded by the fallen angels of Rutinga's loyal slaves."
	TASK_TALK_116	只要干掉他，在鲁廷加解除封印之前，邪恶生物们就群魔无首，不足为患了。	"As long as he was killed, before Rutinga lifted the seal, the evil creatures would be left without their heads."
	TASK_TALK_117	在出发之前，我们应该进一步强化自己的实力。和我一起尝试一下抽奖和强化技能吧！	"Before we go out, we should further strengthen our strength. Let's try the lottery and strengthen our skills with me."
	TASK_TALK_118	还记得亚历克斯么？他最近组织了一个全新的竞技赛事，并邀请你前往参加。你一定要去试试。	Do you remember Alex? He recently organized a brand new competition and invited you to attend. You must try.
	TASK_TALK_119	欢迎参加竞技场！这是一个荟聚了全部要塞英雄们的赛事。你将有机会与其他英雄们同台竞技。	Welcome to the arena! This is a competition that gathers all the heroes of the fortress. You will have the opportunity to compete with other heroes.
	TASK_TALK_120	为了鼓励你们拿到更好的成绩。我们的奖励非常的让人眼红，除了大量的金币资源奖励之外。	"To encourage you to get better grades. Our awards are very eye-catching, in addition to a large number of gold resources awards."
	TASK_TALK_121	我还向科斯塔大人发起了申请，将前三名的雕像树立在要塞的正中间，以供所有人瞻仰膜拜。	I also applied to Lord Costa for the first three statues to be erected in the middle of the fortress for all to worship.
	TASK_TALK_122	所以，听完了这些，你是不是迫不及待了呢！	"So, after listening to these, can't you wait!?"
	TASK_TALK_123	很好！要记得，在不忙的时候来参加竞技场的战斗。今天就到这里吧！科斯塔还等着你和他探讨下一步的计划呢！	Very good! Remember to fight in the arena when you are not busy. Let's call it a day. Costa is waiting for you to discuss with him the next step.
	TASK_TALK_124	我听说荷鲁斯神庙的战事进展的很顺利，这让我感到非常的欣慰。	I am very gratified to hear that the war at the Temple of Horus is progressing smoothly.
	TASK_TALK_125	梅瑟刚刚来找过我。她支支吾吾的，谁也不知道她想说什么。	Moser just came to see me. No one knows what she's trying to say.
	TASK_TALK_126	只是有一点很明确，她指明了要见你。或许她有什么难言之隐，去看看她吧！	Just one thing is clear. She pointed out that she wanted to see you. Maybe she has something to hide. Go and see her.
	TASK_TALK_127	“荷鲁斯神庙-破碎回廊”的镇守头目灵轮盾将曾经是一个人类。在魔化之前，他曾是我的魔法导师。	"The guardian of the ""Horus Temple - Broken Corridor"" will once be a human being. Before demonization, he was my magic teacher."
	TASK_TALK_128	在一次战斗中，他为了保护我被抓住。之后卑鄙的堕落天使就将他魔化改造成了现在的灵轮盾将。	"In a battle, he was caught to protect me. Then the despicable fallen angel demonized him and transformed him into the present spiritual wheel shield."
	TASK_TALK_129	如果可以的话，我希望你不要杀他。带他回来，如对待其他英雄那样，我们可以净化他们。	"I hope you don't kill him if you can. Bring him back, as we do with other heroes, and we can purify them."
	TASK_TALK_130	非常的感谢！伊蕾莎又在满要塞找你，快去吧！	Thank you very much! Eliza is looking for you in the fortress again. Go!
	TASK_TALK_131	喂喂！你怎么总是这么粗心大意！为英雄升阶这种事，果然总是要我来提醒呢!	Hello! Why are you always so careless? It's true that I always want to remind you of the promotion of heroes.
	TASK_TALK_132	嗯！不过我知道，这是因为你想见我故意的对吗？好啦！总之，要记得给英雄升阶哦！	"Uh huh! But I know it's because you want to see me on purpose, right? All right! In short, remember to promote heroes!"
	TASK_TALK_133	又到了令人伤感的分离。不过，为了我们共同的家园，儿女情长……	"It's sad separation again. Nevertheless, for our common home, our children are fond of each other..."
	TASK_TALK_134	咳咳！科斯塔正亢奋的像个神经病一样，你得帮他安静下来。	Cough! Costa is hyperactive like a neurosis. You have to help him calm down.
	TASK_TALK_135	我已经感受到“荷鲁斯神庙-阴暗教廷”的怪物们正在瑟瑟发抖，干掉它们，我们就将直面堕落天使。	"I have already felt that the monsters of Horus Temple, the Dark Holy See, are trembling and destroying them, and we will face the fallen angels."
	TASK_TALK_136	这令人激动的时刻终于到来了，只要解决堕落天使，邪恶生物们将再无回天之力。	"This exciting moment has finally arrived, and as long as the fallen angels are solved, the evil creatures will no longer be able to return to heaven."
	TASK_TALK_137	关于堕落天使，露娜对它很是了解。知己知彼，我可不想你在这么重要的战斗里掉链子，去咨询露娜，找到它的弱点。	Luna knows a lot about the fallen angel. I don't want you to fall out in such an important battle and consult Luna to find out her weaknesses.
	TASK_TALK_138	我的确曾经和堕落天使交过手，但是它的实力太强了，我根本不是对手。我脸上的伤，就是和它战斗造成的。	"I did fight the fallen angel, but it's too powerful. I'm not an opponent at all. The wound on my face was caused by fighting with it."
	TASK_TALK_139	传说它在堕落之前，是一个教廷的主教。所以它精通各种咒语法术。	"Legend has it that before its fall, it was a bishop of the Holy See. So it is proficient in all kinds of spell grammar."
	TASK_TALK_140	或许，近身搏击不是它的强项，你可以试试！	"Perhaps, close combat is not its strong point, you can try!"
	TASK_TALK_141	你做的非常好，希望我的建议在战斗中给你带来了帮助。	You have done very well. I hope my suggestions will help you in the battle.
	TASK_TALK_142	科斯塔正着急的等着你们的喜讯。去告诉他吧！	Costa is eagerly awaiting your good news. Go and tell him!
	TASK_TALK_143	虽然我们一厢情愿的以为击败堕落天使就能结束战斗，但是我仍然要告诉你一些令人难过的消息。	"Although we wishfully believe that defeating the fallen angels will bring the battle to an end, I still want to tell you some sad news."
	TASK_TALK_144	在堕落天使被击败之前，它再一次召唤和蛊惑了本应加入我们的英雄——亚瑟王。	"Before the fallen angel was defeated, it once again called and bewitched King Arthur, the hero who should have joined us."
	TASK_TALK_145	他现在就在“荷鲁斯神庙-裁决之地”。亚瑟王的实力非常强劲，你一定要当心。	"He is now in the ""Temple of Horus - the Land of Judgment"". King Arthur's strength is very strong, you must be careful."
	TASK_TALK_146	侦察兵带回来非常不好的消息，科斯塔正焦头烂额。	The scouts brought back very bad news. Costa was in a state of great anxiety.
	TASK_TALK_147	去帮帮他吧！	Go and help him!
	TASK_TALK_148	就当我以为胜利的曙光就在前方时，我又再一次遭受到沉重的打击。堕落天使在被击败前，已经在时空炼狱准备解锁鲁廷加的封印。	"Just when I thought the dawn of victory was ahead, I was hit hard again. Before being defeated, the fallen angels were already in time and space purgatory ready to unlock Rutinga's seal."
	TASK_TALK_149	我不知道它们的进度如何，但是一定不能在我们到达之前成功解除封印。前往“时空炼狱-岩浆城堡”，一定要快！	"I don't know how they are progressing, but we must not be able to successfully lift the seals before we arrive. Go to ""Time and Space Purgatory - Magma Castle"" quickly!"
	TASK_TALK_150	敌人防御很严密，那就证明它们现在还未成功。否则，以鲁廷加的能量，一定早就采取疯狂报复行动了。	"The enemy's tight defense proves that they have not succeeded yet. Otherwise, with Rutinga's energy, mad retaliation would have taken place long ago."
	TASK_TALK_151	时间紧迫，继续向前探索！下一处是“时空炼狱-熔岩平台”。	"Time is pressing, continue to explore! Next is ""Purgatory of Time and Space - Lava Platform""."
	TASK_TALK_152	可恶！还是没能发现解锁封印的力量吗？抱歉，我需要冷静一下。去找伊蕾莎吧！作为最高顾问，她一定知道怎么办。	"Abhorrent! Or did we not find the power to unlock the blockade? Sorry, I need to calm down. Go and find Eliza! As a top consultant, she must know what to do."
	TASK_TALK_153	情势非常危急。请咬紧牙关！再坚持一下，去探索“时空炼狱-古神尸骸”。	The situation is very critical. Please clench your teeth! Stick to it again and explore the "Purgatory of Time and Space - the remains of ancient gods".
	TASK_TALK_154	先知法奇奥感知到了一些非常关键的信息。	The prophet Fachio perceived some very critical information.
	TASK_TALK_155	快去问问他，究竟负责解锁的敌人们藏在哪里。	Go and ask him where the enemies responsible for unlocking are hiding.
	TASK_TALK_156	我在时空炼狱感知到了一些熟悉的星魂碎片的能量波动。	I sensed the energy fluctuations of some familiar star debris in Purgatory of Time and Space.
	TASK_TALK_157	我想，这一定是在为鲁廷加使用星魂碎片解锁封印。	I think it must be for Rutinga to unlock the blockade with Star Debris.
	TASK_TALK_158	波动的位置就在“时空炼狱-炎阳地牢”。	The position of fluctuation is "Purgatory of Time and Space - Dungeon of Yanyang".
	TASK_TALK_159	很好！果然它们就是那只秘密的解锁封印的力量。现在，去告诉伊蕾莎捷报吧！	"Very good! Sure enough, they are the secret power to unlock the blockade. Now, let's tell Elizabeth the news."
	TASK_TALK_160	他们带领着全部的邪恶军团停留在虚空之城。是时候来个了结了。我已经发动要塞所有力量全面进攻虚空之城。你的目标是“虚空之城-观星台”	They led all the evil legions to stay in the city of void. It's time to finish. I have mobilized all the forces of the fortress to attack the empty city in an all-round way. Your goal is "City of the Void - Observatory"
	TASK_TALK_161	感谢你！感谢你代替我完成了我应该完成的使命。我已经找不到任何词汇来形容和褒奖你们。	Thank you! Thank you for fulfilling my mission instead of me. I can't find any words to describe and praise you.
	TASK_TALK_162	鲁廷加已经被彻底击溃，敌人败局已定……	Rutinga has been completely defeated and the enemy's defeat has been decided...
	TASK_TALK_163	但好像还有些残兵败将在负隅顽抗，去找到科斯塔，告诉他战斗还没结束，他应该醒醒了！	"But it seems that some of the disabled soldiers will fight in the corner, go to Costa and tell him that the battle is not over, he should wake up!"
	TASK_TALK_164	原谅我的失态！但是我知道，作为女神的化身，伊蕾莎一定会带领我们走向胜利。	"Forgive my impoliteness! But I know that as the incarnation of the Goddess, Eliza will lead us to victory."
	TASK_TALK_165	鲁廷加在被消灭之前，还曾蛊惑过传奇英雄斯巴达克斯。现在，他正率领着邪恶生物在“时空炼狱-审判所”赋予顽抗。	"Before Rutinga was wiped out, he also bewitched the legendary hero Spartacus. Now, he is leading evil creatures in the ""Purgatory of Time and Space - Trial House"" to confer resistance."
	TASK_TALK_166	终于…结束了吗？	Finally... Is that over?
	TASK_TALK_167	为了我们共同的家园，为了和平和安定！伊娃女神万岁。	"For our common home, for peace and stability! Long live Eva."
	TASK_TALK_168	或许，你应该见一见伊蕾莎。你们一定有很多话要说。	Maybe you should meet Eliza. You must have a lot to say.
	TASK_TALK_169	你是来庆贺的吗？恐怕你要再一次的失望了。我们低估了鲁廷加，他根本就没有被完全毁灭。那些曾经被蛊惑的英雄们，都被它埋下过灵魂印记。	"Are you here to celebrate? I'm afraid you'll be disappointed again. We underestimated Rutinga, who was not completely destroyed. The heroes who had been bewitched had been imprinted with their souls."
	TASK_TALK_170	现在，他们的意识已经被鲁廷加的灵魂印记吞噬。他们正传承着鲁廷加的意志，想要吞噬我们的家园，我们的星球。	"Now their consciousness has been engulfed by Rutinga's soul imprint. They are inheriting Rutinga's will to devour our our homeland, our planet."
	TASK_TALK_171	糟糕！露娜和她的游侠队伍似乎遇到了麻烦。如果她那边失利，对我们的全盘计划影响很大。	"Too bad! Luna and her Rangers seem to be in trouble. If she fails, it will have a great impact on our overall plan."
	TASK_TALK_172	尽快和她谈谈，帮她的队伍脱困。	Talk to her as soon as possible to help her team out of trouble.
	TASK_TALK_173	在最后一次的决战中，根据伊蕾莎的指示，风暴要塞投入全部的力量全线进攻。	"In the last decisive battle, according to Eliza's instructions, Storm Fortress put all its strength into full attack."
	TASK_TALK_174	我和我的游侠团在“虚空之城-风暴台”遭到了敌人强力的阻击。我们的实力太弱了，队伍很轻易就被击溃，敌人即将反扑和增援其他区域。	My Rangers and I were strongly blocked by the enemy in the "City of the Void-Storm". Our strength is too weak. Our troops are easily defeated. The enemy is about to fight back and reinforce other areas.
	TASK_TALK_175	我非常需要你们的帮助，去将“虚空之城-风暴台”的敌人全部消灭。	I really need your help to wipe out all the enemies of the "Void City - Storm Turret".
	TASK_TALK_176	你们及时的帮助挽救了整个局势。	Your timely help saved the whole situation.
	TASK_TALK_177	但是，形势仍然不乐观。亚历克斯似乎陷入了僵局。	"However, the situation is still not optimistic. Alex seems to be in a deadlock."
	TASK_TALK_178	终于等到你们了。我和我的角斗士队伍成功的在“虚空之城-漩涡台”围困了敌人。	It's finally up to you. My team of gladiators and I succeeded in besieging the enemy in the Void City-Whirlpool Platform.
	TASK_TALK_179	但是因为敌人实力太强，我们多次尝试都无法剿灭。我不敢冒风险，以至于到现在仍然一直僵持。	"But because the enemy's strength is too strong, we can't exterminate it after many attempts. I dare not take risks, so that I still have a deadlock."
	TASK_TALK_180	请出手吧！帮助我们战胜他们。	Please do it! Help US defeat them.
	TASK_TALK_181	非常感谢你们。没有你们的帮助，我无法完成我的任务。	"Thank you very much. Without your help, I couldn't accomplish my task."
	TASK_TALK_182	听说先知法奇奥和他的法师学徒们打了个大胜仗，但是他依然觉得很苦恼！去看看这个老头到底为什么烦恼。	"I heard that the prophet Fachio and his apprentices had won a great battle, but he still felt very distressed! Let's see why the old man is upset."
	TASK_TALK_183	原来打赢了也有这么多苦恼。敌人的主力在正面交锋中被我和我的学徒们击溃。	The original win also has so many distresses. The main force of the enemy was defeated by me and my apprentices in a frontal confrontation.
	TASK_TALK_184	但是他们却化整为零，分散在开来频频骚扰。我和我的学徒们正头疼该如何把他们一网打尽。	"But they are all zero, scattered in the open frequency of harassment. My apprentices and I are having a headache about how to get rid of them all."
	TASK_TALK_185	这种事，你一定非常擅长。去帮助我剿灭“虚空之城-魔法师平台”的残兵游勇。	You must be very good at this kind of thing. To help me eradicate the "Void City - Magician Platform" of the disabled.
	TASK_TALK_186	多谢你！没有你们的帮助，我这把老骨头恐怕会耗死在这里。	"Thank you! Without your help, I'm afraid my old bone will be consumed here."
	TASK_TALK_187	科斯塔似乎在准备最后的总攻，正等着咱们的捷报。快去通知他。	"Costa seems to be preparing for the final offensive, waiting for our briefing. Let him know."
	TASK_TALK_188	感谢你所做的一切，现在我们已经胜券在握。敌人已经牢牢的被我们困在最后两个虚空平台。	Thank you for all you have done. Now we have the chance to win. The enemy is firmly trapped in the last two empty platforms.
	TASK_TALK_189	趁热打铁，不能让他们有任何的机会撤离。毕竟，那可是鲁廷加的意识分身。	"Strike while the iron is hot. They can't get any chance to evacuate. After all, that's Rutinga's conscious identity."
	TASK_TALK_190	前往“虚空之城-封印台”，不能留下任何后患！	"Go to the ""empty city - Seal Desk"", can not leave any aftermath!"
	TASK_TALK_191	这次，是真的快结束了吗？	Is it really coming to an end this time?
	TASK_TALK_192	最后下达结束这一切指令的人，必然是女神的化身伊蕾莎。	"The person who finally gave the order to end all this must be Eliza, the incarnation of the goddess."
	TASK_TALK_193	你说，当一切回归原样。风暴要塞将何去何从？各个时空位面的英雄们，又将何去何从？我又将何去何从？我舍不得……	"You say, when everything goes back to its original state. Where will the storm fortress go? Where will the heroes of every space-time plane go? Where will I go? I can't bear to..."
	TASK_TALK_194	哎！这种头痛的问题还是胜利之后再去想吧！现在，我们只需要前往“虚空之城-决战台”，击败敌人并获得胜利！	"Hey! Let's think about this headache after victory. Now, all we need to do is go to the ""Void City - Final Platform"" to defeat the enemy and win!"
	TASK_TALK_195	可恶！！！没想到，它们在最后一刻成功的帮助鲁廷加解除了封印。	"Abhorrent!!! Unexpectedly, they succeeded in helping Rutinga lift the seal at the last minute."
	TASK_TALK_196	有个秘密我隐瞒了大家很久。我，伊蕾莎，其实只是伊娃沉睡后的意识分身。	"I kept a secret from you for a long time. I, Eliza, am just a conscious part of Eva after she falls asleep."
	TASK_TALK_197	也可以说，我就是伊娃。可是我现在毫无神力。	"In other words, I am Eva. But I'm powerless now."
	TASK_TALK_198	但是我一点儿也没感到绝望。	But I didn't feel any despair.
	TASK_TALK_199	因为，我能感受到星核神力它还存在。那些我熟悉又迷恋的力量，它就在你们的体内……	Because I can feel the power of the Star Nucleus and it still exists. The forces that I know and love are within you...
	TASK_TALK_200	我早该发现，当你们这些英雄逐渐成长，通过星魂碎片不断强化进步，其实就早已融合了我所拥有的全部星核神力。	"I should have found that when you heroes grow up and progress through the debris of the Star and Soul, in fact, they have already integrated all the power of the Star and Nucleus that I possess."
	TASK_TALK_201	对抗鲁廷加的战斗，最终是属于你们的！	The battle against Rutinga belongs to you in the end!
	TASK_TALK_202	战斗吧！英雄们，为了你的故事不随肉体毁灭而消亡，为了你的传说新添耀眼光芒……	"Fight! Heroes, for your story does not die with the destruction of the body, for your legend add a shining light..."
	TASK_TALK_203	恭喜通过最终试炼，正式成为要塞的一员。棒棒哒！	Congratulations on being a member of the fortress through the final trial. Awesome!
	TASK_TALK_204	刚才的战斗中得到了一些物品。这都是能增强实力的好东西。	I got some items in the battle just now. These are all good things to enhance strength.
	TASK_TALK_205	现在，去学会使用它们强化装备吧！	"Now, learn to use them to strengthen equipment."
	TASK_TALK_206	达芬奇的情绪已经稳定了很多，他似乎已经恢复了意识。	Da Vinci's mood has stabilized a lot and he seems to have regained consciousness.
	TASK_TALK_207	科斯塔大人听说了这件事，正想找你聊聊后续的计划！	Lord Costa has heard about this and is looking for you to talk about the follow-up plan!
	TASK_TALK_208	在虚空大陆上生存，不结识一帮可靠的伙伴怎么行，点击好友查找添加有缘分的好友吧	"To survive in the empty land, how can we not meet a group of reliable partners? Click on friends to find friends with fate."
	TASK_TALK_209	添加好友后每天可给每一个好友赠送一次体力哦，当然也能接受好友赠送的体力，双方受益呢	"After adding friends, you can give each friend a gift of physical strength every day. Of course, you can also accept the gift of physical strength from friends. Both sides benefit from it."
