#	字典配置表		
#	Key		Value
#	string		string
#	字典主键	策划备注	字典内容，可使用转义符
	PROPAGANDA_BATTLE_001	去我们身后的战场保护自由圣旗，一切为自由而战。	Go to the battlefield behind us and protect the flag of freedom. Everything is fighting for freedom.
	PROPAGANDA_BATTLE_002	敌袭！敌袭！一起应战！	Enemy attack! Enemy attack! Fight together!
	PROPAGANDA_BATTLE_003	这里暂时安全，赶紧去帮助其他英灵战胜异魔！	It's safe here for the time being. Help other spirits defeat the devil!
	PROPAGANDA_BATTLE_004	哈哈哈哈！梅林，凭你就想挡住我吗？去死吧！	"Ha ha ha ha! Merlin, do you want to stop me? Go to hell!"
	PROPAGANDA_BATTLE_005	区区异魔，看我破你诡计！	Watch me break your trick!
	PROPAGANDA_BATTLE_006	闯入者？小的们，干掉他！	"The intruder? Kill him, boys!"
	PROPAGANDA_BATTLE_007	等候多时了！	How long have you been waiting?
	PROPAGANDA_BATTLE_009	一群废物，最后还得我自己动手。	"A bunch of waste, and finally I have to do it myself."
	PROPAGANDA_BATTLE_010	你的好运到此结束了！	That's the end of your good fortune!
	PROPAGANDA_BATTLE_011	拿开你的脏手！那是我的宝藏！	Take away your dirty hands! That's my treasure!
	PROPAGANDA_BATTLE_012	嘁！区区一个分身，看我灭了你！	Hey! Watch me kill you!
	PROPAGANDA_BATTLE_013	圣洁的法灵啊，净化吧！救赎吧！	"Purify, Holy Spirit of the law! Redemption!"
	PROPAGANDA_BATTLE_014	这片暗淡的世界，只因有你，我愿化作一瞬的烟火！	"This dark world, just because of you, I would like to turn into a flash of fireworks!"
	PROPAGANDA_BATTLE_015	我本阴影，一起，归于黑暗！	"My shadow, together, belongs to the darkness!"
	PROPAGANDA_BATTLE_016	堂堂正正，一较高下！	"Be honest and upright, be higher and lower!"
	PROPAGANDA_BATTLE_017	堂堂正正，一较高下！	"Be honest and upright, be higher and lower!"
	PROPAGANDA_BATTLE_018	吾王在上，容我再添荣光！	Let me add glory to my king!
	PROPAGANDA_BATTLE_019	打败你，人民就能过上好日子吗？	"If you are defeated, will the people live a good life?"
	PROPAGANDA_BATTLE_020	为了自由，圣战吧！	"For freedom, jihad!"
	PROPAGANDA_BATTLE_021	嗷！我……不会……死！不会！！	Oh! I... No... Die! Can't!!
	PROPAGANDA_BATTLE_022	大人！救我……	Adult! Help me...
	PROPAGANDA_BATTLE_023	地狱之火，锻我筋骨，幽冥鬼风，凝我精魄！我，永生不死！	"Hell fire, forge my bones and muscles, ghost wind, condense my soul! I will never die!"
	PROPAGANDA_BATTLE_024	的确是我吸走了狮心王的英魂，当英魂全部被吸走，你就知道为什么我必须要踏入魔域了，想知道答案就看你的能耐！！	"It is true that I have sucked the spirit of the Lion Heart King. When all the souls are sucked away, you will know why I have to step into the magic realm. To know the answer depends on your ability!!"
	PROPAGANDA_STORY_001	亚瑟	Arthur
	PROPAGANDA_TUTORIAL_001	哈哈，终于又可以并肩作战了，我一按耐不住了！	"Haha, finally we can fight together again. I can't help it!"
	PROPAGANDA_TUTORIAL_002	还是要靠你先打个头阵哦~	It's still up to you to make a start.~
