#	字典配置表		
#	Key		Value
#	string		string
#	字典主键	策划备注	字典内容，可使用转义符
	UI_SIGN_HEALTH_GAME_TITLE_TEXT	健康游戏忠告	Health Game Advice
	UI_SIGN_HEALTH_GAME_TEXT	抵制不良游戏，拒绝盗版游戏。注意自我保护，谨防受骗上当。适度游戏益脑，沉迷游戏伤身。合理安排时间，享受健康生活。	"Resist bad games, refuse pirated games. Pay attention to self-protection and guard against being deceived. Moderate games benefit the brain, indulge in games hurt the body. Reasonable arrangement of time, enjoy a healthy life."
	UI_AGREEMENT_CONTENT	一、[4EFF4AFF]特别提示[-]`NL`1、本公司同意按照本协议的规定及其不时发布的操作规则提供基于互联网的相关 服务(以下称“网络服务”)，为获得网络服务，您同意本协议的全部条款并按照页面上的提示完成全部的注册程序。您在进行注册程序过程中点击“同意”按钮即表示用户完全接受本协议项下的全部条款。这些条款可由本公司随时更新，协议条款一旦发生变动，本公司将会在相关的页面上提示变更内容。修改后的协议一旦在页面上公布即有效代替原来的协议。您在使用本公司提供的软件产品之前，应仔细阅读本协议，如不同意本服务协议及或随时对其的修改，请停止使用本公司提供的服务内容。`NL`二、权属声明`NL`1、本公司定义的服务内容包括：文字、软件、声音、相片、录像、图表、版式 结构；在广告中的全部内容；电子邮件的全部内容；本公司游戏服务为客户提供的商业信息。所有这些内容均受版权、商标、和其它财产所有权法律的保护。用户只有在获得本公司或相关权利人的书面授权之后才能使用这些内容。`NL`2、本公司发布的所有软件，包括本公司网络游戏客户端软件等所有客户端软件均受中华人民共和国版权法保护，用户可以下载并使用，但未经本公司许可，用户不得修改本公司游戏的客户端程序；不得制作、传播或使用扰 乱正常游戏秩序或有损本公司利益的任何第三方软件。	"1. [4EFF4AFF] Special Tips [-] `NL`1. The Company agrees to provide Internet-based related services (hereinafter referred to as ""network services"") in accordance with the provisions of this Agreement and the operating rules issued from time to time. In order to obtain network services, you agree to all the terms of this Agreement and complete all registration procedures according to the prompts on the page. When you click the ""Agree"" button during the registration process, the user accepts all the terms and conditions under this agreement. These terms can be updated by our company at any time. Once the terms of the agreement are changed, we will prompt for the change on the relevant pages. Once the revised protocol is published on the page, it will effectively replace the original protocol. Before using the software products provided by our company, you should read this agreement carefully. If you do not agree with this service agreement and change it at any time, please stop using the service provided by our company. ` NL `2, Ownership Statement `NL `1. The company defines services including: text, software, sound, photos, videos, charts, format structure; all content in advertising; all content of e-mail; business information provided by the company's game services to customers. All these contents are protected by copyright, trademark and other property ownership laws. Users can only use these contents after they have obtained written authorization from the company or the relevant obligee. ` NL`2. All software released by the company, including the company's online game client software and other client software, are protected by the Copyright Law of the People's Republic of China. Users may download and use the software, but without the company's permission, users may not modify the company's game client program; they may not produce, disseminate or use any task that disrupts the normal order of the game or impairs the company's interests. What third-party software?"
	UI_NOTICE_CONTENT	欢迎进入游戏，您的支持是我们最大的动力！	"Welcome to the game, your support is our greatest motivation!"
	UI_AGREEMENT_READ_FULL_TEXT	已阅读全文	Read the full text
	UI_GAME_ANNOUNCEMENT	用户协议	User Protocol
	UI_USER_AGREEMENT	游戏公告	Game announcement
	UI_TEXT_UPDATE_RESOURCE	正在更新游戏资源 {4:P2}，{0}/{1}，{2}/{3}，{5}/s，大约还需 {6}。	"Game resources {4:P2}, {0}/{1}, {2}/{3}, {5}/s are being updated, and about {6} is needed."
	UI_TEXT_SECOND	{0} 秒	{0} seconds
	UI_TEXT_MINUTE_SECOND	{0} 分 {1} 秒	{0} minutes {1} seconds
	UI_TEXT_HOUR_MINUTE	{0} 小时 {1} 分	{0} hours {1} points
	UI_TEXT_FATAL_ERROR	出现严重错误，需要重新启动游戏，如果继续运行，可能产生未知错误。{0}{1}	"Serious errors occur and the game needs to be restarted. If it continues to run, unknown errors may occur. {0}{1}"
	UI_TEXT_RETRY	重试	retry
	UI_TEXT_RESTART	重新启动	Restart
	UI_TEXT_DONOT_RESTART	继续运行	Continue running
	UI_TEXT_SELECT_PUBLISHER	请选择版本	Please select the version.
	UI_TEXT_OUTER_SERVER	外网服务器	Extranet Server
	UI_TEXT_INNER_SERVER	测试服务器	Test Server
	UI_TEXT_FORCE_GAME_UPDATE	您当前的游戏版本不再被支持，请通过 http://ota.antinc.cn/ 更新最新的游戏版本。	Your current version of the game is no longer supported. Please update the latest version of the game through http://ota.antinc.cn/.
	UI_TEXT_VERIFY_INNER_VERSION_FAILED	您当前的游戏版本与适用版本({0})不一致，请通过 http://ota.antinc.cn/ 更新最新的游戏版本。	Your current version of the game does not match the applicable version ({0}). Please update the latest version of the game through http://ota.antinc.cn/.
	UI_TEXT_GOTO_UPDATE	我要更新	I want to update
	UI_TEXT_QUIT_GAME	暂时退出	Temporary withdrawal
	UI_TEXT_EXIT_GAME	退出游戏	Exit the game
	UI_TEXT_CONTINUE_DOWNLOAD	继续下载	Continue downloading
	UI_TEXT_NETWORK_NOT_REACHABLE	当前网络不可用，请检查后重试。	The current network is not available. Please check and try again.
	UI_TEXT_NETWORK_REACHABLE_VIA_CARRIER_DATA_NETWORK	您当前使用的是移动蜂窝网络，将要下载 {0} 资源，是否继续？	You are currently using a mobile cellular network. You will download {0} resources. Do you want to continue?
	UI_BUTTON_SERVER_HOT	[FF4B33FF]爆满[-]	[FF4B33FF] Full [-]
	UI_BUTTON_SERVER_FLUENT	[71FF33FF]流畅[-]	[71FF33FF] Fluent [-]
	UI_BUTTON_SERVER_MAINTENANCE	维护	Maintain
	UI_TEXT_ACCOUNT	账号	Account number
	UI_TEXT_PASSWORD	密码	Password
	UI_BUTTON_SWITCHACCOUNT	[u]更换账号[/u]	[u] Replacement of account [/u]
	UI_BUTTON_NOTICE	[u]公告[/u]	[u] Announcement [/u]
	UI_BUTTON_CHANGESERVER	换区	Change zone
	UI_BUTTON_STARTGAME	开始游戏	Start the game
	UI_BUTTON_CONFIRMLOGIN	确认登录	Confirm login
	UI_BUTTON_ACCOUNT_NAME_IS_INVALID	账号非法，请重新输入。	The account is illegal. Please re-enter it.
	UI_TEXT_NETWORK_DISCONNECTED	网络连接已断开，是否重新连接？	The network connection has been disconnected. Do you want to reconnect?
	UI_TEXT_NETWORK_RECONNECTTING	网络连接重连中……	Network connection reconnection...
	UI_TEXT_RECONNECT	重新连接	Reconnection
	UI_TITLE_NAME_SELECTSERVER	服务器列表	Server List
	UI_SIGN_CONSTITUENCY	{0}区	{0} area
	UI_SIGN_SELECT_A_LARGE_AREA	{0}-{1}区	{0} - {1} region
	UI_SIGN_RECOMMENDED_AREA	推荐服	Recommended clothes
	UI_TEXT_SERVER_LASTTIME	上次登录：	Last logon:
	UI_TEXT_SERVER_HADPLAYERS	仅显示创建过角色的服务器	Show only servers that have created roles
	UI_TEXT_SERVER_NOTE_MAINTENANCE	该服务器目前处于维护中，敬请谅解	"The server is currently in maintenance, please forgive me."
	UI_BUTTON_OTHER	其他	Other
	UI_BUTTON_CONFIRM	确定	Sure?
	UI_BUTTON_CANCEL	取消	cancel
	UI_OH_I_SEE	我知道了	I got it!
	UI_USER_AGREEMENT_AGREE	同意	Agree
	UI_TEXT_RESTART_SURE	连接服务器失败。点击‘确定’按钮重新启动游戏	The connection to the server failed. Click on the'OK'button to restart the game
	UI_TEXT_RECONNECTION	连接网络失败。请确认网络连接并点击'重试'按钮	The connection network failed. Please confirm the network connection and click the'retry'button
